I'm going, Nanamin.
You can't.
I already explained why this morning.
If a veil has been cast,
there's a strong possibility that
he's alive and at Satozakura High School.
I'll be back soon.
Please wait there, Itadori.
It was probably pointless to ask.
You heard the reason,
so I'll leave the rest of this to you, Ino.
Huh?!
Is there a problem with that?
Well, the count of them...
There's a lot.
And they're all humans, right?
I wouldn't mind approving
your first-grade recommendation.
Let's get this done, baby! Hell yeah!
Please step aside, Mr. Ijichi.
Our job is to help others.
That includes students like yourself.
I won't make the same mistake again.
You must not go, Itadori.
Sorry, Mr. Ijichi.
What are you doing, Junpei?!
Stay out of this, jujutsu sorcerer.
Moon Dregs!
A jellyfish beast?
Blunt attacks won't work when he's inside it?
Don't make me repeat myself.
Stay out of this, jujutsu sorcerer!
It's none of your business!
That's not something you get to decide!
What's the point of thoughtlessly saving people?
Don't mistake the value of life!
People pretend their emotions are everything,
but the heart is just the metabolism of the soul.
It's all a delusion!
I will not be restricted by such delusional rules.
If someone deserves to die,
no one has the right to stop it.
So go ahead and take a nap.
There's something I need to take care of.
Your cursed technique is poison.
Your cursed beast can secrete poison
created by cursed energy from their tentacles.
In time you'll learn to control their size, strength, and the potency of your poison.
I can teach you the skills that take years for normal sorcerers to learn,
so you'll be ready to fight right away.
Junpei, you're talented.
Who are you making those excuses for?
Why?
Why won't Moon Dregs' poison work on him?
Why are you getting in my way?
Why?!
He won't be able to dodge midair!
No, I'll take him out right before he lands!
Junpei, I don't understand...
a damn thing you're saying!
You can't string together whatever logic you want.
When facing cursed beast users, strike the sorcerer directly.
But you're just trying...
to convince yourself you're in the right!
I don't know why you're doing this.
You must have a reason.
But is it really worth
throwing away that life you have?
The human heart is a delusion?
Can you say that in front of her?!
People don't have hearts.
You're still—
They don't!
Otherwise...
That would mean people cursed me and my mom with those hearts!
That would just be too much...
I don't know what is right and what is wrong anymore!
Why didn't you dodge it?
Sorry.
I said a lot of self-important stuff
without knowing what you're going through.
But you can talk to me.
I promise I won't judge you, no matter what.
So please.
No way... Your mom...
Junpei, come to Jujutsu Tech.
There are lots of crazy strong teachers and reliable friends there.
If we all work together,
I'm sure we can find whoever cursed your mom.
We'll make sure they get their due!
Let's fight together!
Who are you?
Who is that?
A human?
I guess it's nice to meet you...
No, something feels strange.
Sukuna's vessel.
Mahito, wait!
I'm such an idiot!
A human-like cursed spirit with a patchwork face!
This is exactly like Nanamin described!
Junpei, run!
I don't know how you know this guy,
but right now, just run away!
Please!
Itadori, please calm down!
Mahito's not a bad person...
Bad... person...
You know, you've got a good head on your shoulders.
But overthinking things instead of acting
can put you in some pretty bad spots.
This is the perfect example of that!
You're almost as stupid
as those people you call stupid yourself.
That's why you're gonna die.
Idle Transfiguration.
Now, time for round two.
Junpei...
Junpei!
Get a hold of yourself!
I'll heal you right now!
Sukuna.
Sukuna!
What?
I'll do anything!
You can do whatever you want with me!
So heal Junpei like you did when you restored my heart!
I refuse!
Why you...
Good.
He's completely forgotten about that pact.
How very amusing!
You'd offer up your pride,
your future, your everything, to try to rely on me.
And you can't save anything!
He refused the pact?
It's not like he couldn't do something about it using a reverse cursed technique.
Maybe he can't heal others?
How sad!
You couldn't be more pathetic, brat!
Though, what I'm after is what comes next,
so I guess this works fine.
Oh, I almost forgot.
At the end of the day,
these guys are, and always will be
curses.
Yuji.
Why?
Oh, dead already?
I guess I was kinda rough when I transfigured him.
Guess that's how it goes.
That was an unusual attack.
Interesting!
Too bad that won't work on me.
As long as I maintain the shape of my—
What's going on?!
Did he somehow hit my soul?
That's it!
Itadori Yuji is a vessel.
His body constantly houses another soul in addition to his own.
So naturally...
You've learned to perceive
of the contours of the soul!
The words that came out next were from so deep inside of me
that it made everything
I've ever said up until this point
feel like a complete lie.
I'm gonna kill you!
Don't you mean you'll "exorcise" me, jujutsu sorcerer?
Itadori Yuji has no regard for his own life.
Geto didn't want me using
a hostage to force him into a pact.
If he confronts an invincible enemy he hates so much that he wants to kill him,
will he turn to Sukuna?
If Junpei isn't enough to trigger him,
I'll make him watch as I mutilate every student, one by one.
And while he's seething with hatred,
I'll force him into negotiating a pact with Sukuna.
That should help us win Sukuna over, just as planned.
Though, all of that presumes that I'm stronger than him.
So why did he have to be
my natural enemy!
He keeps distorting his body!
Should I stop trying to grab and throw him?
Now that I know his attacks work on me,
growing in size and giving him
a bigger target isn't a good idea.
In that case...
Doesn't matter if it takes a hundred times or a thousand,
I'll keep attacking him
until I take him down!
I need a form more honed toward murder.
A form inspired to kill!
I'll embody it!
You can't stretch out forever!
Most people would let go, you know.
Overextending myself makes me
lose control and weakens my durability.
You can't beat me.
Just swap out already
with Sukuna.
Idle Transfiguration.
You dare attempt to touch my soul?
Since we both shared a laugh at that brat's expense,
I'll allow it just this once.
There won't be a second time.
Know your place,
insolent fool.
I'm not swapping out.
I already told you...
that I'm gonna kill you.
Huh?
Nanamin!
I'll lecture you later.
What's the situation?
I couldn't save Junpei and his mom.
Always putting others before himself.
Explain your physical condition first.
I'm fine. Just got some holes in me.
How is that fine?
Also, a bunch of students from this school are knocked out in the gym.
Hey, you're alive and well, Seven-Three Sorcerer!
Glad to see we both survived.
How about a hug?
Let's celebrate our reunion!
Itadori, why is his nose bleeding?
Huh? Because I punched him.
When?
At the start of our fight.
Did his hand touch you?
Yeah.
My attacks don't work on him.
Huh?!
What?! Why?!
I'll explain while I'm lecturing you.
Either his technique doesn't work on Itadori,
or he has a reason not to kill him.
Either way, that is to our advantage.
However, I can halt his movements.
Once we've created an opening, we'll shower him with blows.
We'll make sure to exorcise him right here.
Got it!