Our window verified the cursed womb three hours ago.
Once ninety percent were successfully evacuated, they made the call to seal off the center.
Citizens within a 500 meter radius
have been evacuated as well.
Mr. Ijichi, question.
What's a window here?
A window is a member of
Jujutsu Tech who can see curses.
They aren't sorcerers, though.
Oh, okay.
Let's continue.
Detainee Block 2.
At present, five of them
remain inside with the cursed womb.
If this cursed womb is the type that metamorphoses, we predict it will become a special-grade curse.
Special grade.
Hey, so, I still don't understand what "special grade" means.
Then allow me to explain it on idiot level.
Let's start from fourth grade:
A wooden bat is enough for them.
Third grade: If you have a handgun, you can rest easy.
Second grade: It'll be a close call with a shotgun.
First grade: Even a tank may be insufficient.
Then there is special grade.
Let's say you might be on even footing
if you carpet bomb it with cluster bombs.
That's crazy!
Normally, a sorcerer on par with
the curse would take on the mission.
On a day like today, that'd be Mr. Gojo.
I-I see.
So, where is he?
Away on business.
Oh?
He's not someone who should be
loafing around at school in the first place.
Don't expect any souvenirs!
Our line of work is always lacking in manpower.
You will often have to undertake missions that are beyond your level.
This particular case, however,
is an abnormal one and most urgent.
Do not fight under any circumstances.
When confronted by a special-grade,
you either run or you die.
Please, listen to your fears.
Do not forget that your mission here
is strictly the verification and rescue of survivors.
Excuse me!
Excuse me, where is Tadashi?!
Ma'am, you need to stay back!
Please stay back!
Where is Tadashi? Is my son all right?!
Please calm down!
Hey, stop it!
Let go of me!
Please stay back! It's dangerous!
Let me through!
She's a guardian who was here for a visit.
Please step away.
There's a possibility that someone has spread poisonous gas throughout the center.
We cannot share any more details at this time.
No...
Why?
Why is this happening?!
Fushiguro, Kugisaki.
We're gonna save them!
Damn right.
Be careful.
I'll put up a Veil.
Emerge from the darkness that is darker than black.
Purify that which is impure.
It's getting dark!
It's a Veil.
There's a residential area nearby.
This barrier conceals us from the outside world.
That's incredible!
How ignorant.
Divine Dogs!
He'll let us know if the curse gets close.
Oh, I see!
Good boy, good boy! We're counting on you, okay?
Let's go.
Wait!
What is this?
Wh-What's going on in here?
Isn't this a two-story building?
C-C-Calm down! It's a maisonette.
No, it's not.
It's an Innate Domain made from cursed energy.
I've never seen one this big.
Watch the door!
Th-The door's gone!
How?! We just came in through there, didn't we?!
What to do? Hey, hey! What to do?
It'll be fine.
This dog remembers the scent of the entrance.
Oh, my!
Good boy! Have some jerky!
Have all the jerky you want!
Now you're way too calm!
You're so dependable, Fushiguro.
Thanks to you, we'll be able to
save people and save ourselves as well.
Let's keep moving.
Atrocious.
That's... three people, right?
Is Tadashi... Is my son Tadashi all right?!
We're bringing this body back.
What?
It's that woman's son.
But...
His face isn't that messed up.
She won't accept it
if we just tell her that her son is dead.
We have to find and verify two more.
Leave that body behind.
Quit messing around!
We turned around and
the way we got in here was gone!
We won't be able to come back for it later!
I never said we'd come back!
I said leave it behind!
He's not even worth saving alive.
Why the hell would I save his dead body?
Not worth saving? Care to explain?!
This is a juvenile detention center.
Sorcerers are granted access to all information about the scene beforehand.
This Okazaki Tadashi hit a little girl on her way home from school while driving without a license.
And that was his second offense
of driving without license.
I know you're stuck on saving lots of people and guiding them to proper deaths.
But what will you do when someone you saved today kills someone else in the future?
Then why did you save me?!
Cut it out!
Jeez, what are you two doing?!
Have you both totally lost it?
This isn't the time or the place—
Kugisaki?
No way! My Divine Dog should've sensed it!
Itadori!
We're running!
We'll search for Kugisaki la—
It's a special-grade. No doubt about it.
I can't move.
Move it.
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Help people.
Itadori?
Come on, where am I?
It's so dark, I can't see a damn thing.
I sense a curse!
How can there be so many?!
Nue!
Don't die on me. Itadori, Kugisaki!
It has already closed the distance.
No running away now.
Hey, Sukuna! If I die, you die too, right?
If you don't want that, then help me out!
No way.
Even if the parts of me inside you die,
I still have eighteen other fragments of my soul.
That said, I'm not in control of this body.
If you want to switch, go ahead and switch.
But as soon as you do,
I'll kill that brat before the cursed spirit can.
Then I'll go for the girl.
She's got spunk. I'll have fun with her.
Like hell I'm gonna let you do that.
I bet.
But if you get too distracted with me,
your friends might actually die.
It wasn't even a cursed technique.
That was just a blast of pure cursed energy.
Fushiguro!
Take Kugisaki and get out of here!
I'll keep this thing busy until you two are clear.
As soon as you're out, give me some kinda signal.
Once you do, I'll switch with Sukuna.
There's no way you can do this!
Not with only one arm against a special-grade!
Look at it.
It's having fun. It's obviously underestimating us.
Buying some time shouldn't be too hard.
No!
Fushiguro!
Please.
Divine Dogs!
Find Kugisaki!
This is my last one.
Guess I should've brought more.
Easier to move around in your underwear?
What do I do now?
I have no clue how to use cursed energy.
But that's okay for now.
I just have to buy ti—
What was that? A barrier of cursed energy?
Ow, ow, ow.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
Why am I even...
If only I hadn't picked up that finger back then.
If I hadn't eaten it.
If only...
If only.
Stop!
Don't think about it!
No! No!
I wanna run! I wanna run! I wanna run!
I don't want to die!
If I die here...
If I actually died...
Would that be a proper death?!
Stop thinking!
Help people.
Was I really this weak?
I'll remember your face.
I swear I'll curse you!
We're getting out of here, Kugisaki!
I'm not a fan of frogs, y'know.
Yeah, well, too bad!
I was so full of myself.
I thought I was strong.
At least strong enough to die on my own terms.
But I was wrong.
I'm weak!
I'm far too weak!
Augh, I don't wanna die!
No! No way!
But...
I'm about to.
A proper death?
Yeah, right. Don't be naive!
Jujutsu sorcerers never die without regret.
Still, to be able to say my death was a proper one...
Curses are born from humanity's negative emotions.
I'll take all the hate, fear, and regret
and let it all out
with this fist!
Damn it!
That howl...
It's Fushiguro's signal.
What a thoroughly annoying brat.
He's obviously screwing around with me.
Hold on a moment. I'm thinking right now.
What can I do to make him regret this?
If I went after him, the brat would just switch back.
So the most troublesome situation for him would be...
this, of course.
I'll put things back the way they were.
Come, let's go kill the brats.
Follow me.
You fool!
Ah, shit. I healed this one too.
You don't like going out for strolls?
Well, I guess curses are
supposed to linger at their point of origin.
Fine, fine. In that case,
you can die here!
Hey, what's the matter?
You're not finished already, are you?
That's it. Come on, you can do better.
Even a cursed spirit...
would miss losing an arm, right?
Please expand the evacuation area to 10 kilometers.
What about you?
I'm waiting here for Itadori to return.
I see.
In that case, after I drop Kugisaki at the hospital,
I'll come back as quickly as possible.
No, there wouldn't be much point in you being here.
If you want to help, please ask them
to send a first-grade sorcerer or higher.
Not that I imagine any are around.
I'll do what I can.
Later.
In the worst-case scenario...
I don't want him to die.
Yes, it's personal. Please do something about it.
...it'll be my responsibility to end him.
Hey, did you know?
We're both classified as "special grade," apparently.
Both you and me, man.
Good job, special-grade!
Keep at it. You can do it.
You look pleased. Want me to praise you?
Healing yourself with cursed energy isn't that hard for curses, unlike humans.
Neither you nor this brat
has the slightest idea of what a curse can do.
This is a good opportunity, so allow me to give you
a taste of true jujutsu sorcery.
Domain Expansion:
Malevolent Shrine!
I was only going for three slices,
but jeez, man, you're weak.
Oh, yeah, and then there's this.
I'll be taking this.
It's over.
This sucks!
If you're gonna switch, just do it already!
What's the matter, brat?
Juju Stroll.
Yes, yes, understood.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
Stare
What's the matter?
You bow while on the phone?
I just get so wrapped up in creating
the feeling of being-on-the-phone, you know?
I know what you mean.
I've hurt my neck several times
dealing with ingrown hairs while depilating.
Of course, I've hurt my pores, too.
How are they related?
I've noticed you often sound irritated on calls.
You can thank Mr. Gojo for that.
And you usually wander around when you're on call.
Speaking of phones,
can you stay on a call while
holding the phone against your shoulder?