*If Conventional Weapons Were Effective Against Cursed Spirits
Grade 4
A wooden bat is enough
Grade 3
If you have a handgun, you can rest easy
Grade 2
Close call with a shotgun
Grade 1
Even a tank may be insufficient
Close call with a shotgun
Grade 1
Even a tank may be insufficient
Special-Grade
Even footing with a carpet bombing of cluster bombs
Block 2
Episode 4: Curse Womb Must Die
Okazaki Tadashi
Youth's Name | Date of Birth
Okazaki Tadashi | August 9th, 2001
Highest Education | Sakakidate High School
Date of Detention | July 20, 2017
Family History | Only has his birth mother, Okazaki Chisaki (42)...
...gone missing, and cannot be contacted...
...living with his mother in an apartment in Eishuu City...
Juju Stroll
Episode 5:
Curse Womb Must Die -II-