Tokyo Metropolitan
Jujutsu Technical High School
400 Yen Corner
Episode 3: Girl of Steel
Kugisaki's POV
Tokyo
Roppongi
Kugisaki
Broken Van
Filth
Serves you right
Go back to Tokyo
Leave
This bridge is dangerous
due to deterioration from age
and can no longer be used.
Sticker Book
We Protest the Kitagawa Highway Extension!
Home for Sale
Broken Van
Filth
Serves you right
Go back to Tokyo
Leave
This bridge is dangerous
due to deterioration from age
and can no longer be used.
Harajuku
Coin Locker
Log: July 2018
West Tokyo City
Eishuu Juvenile Detention Center
In the sky above the exercise yard
Unnamed Apparition of Potential Special Grade
Its curse womb was witnessed by several non-jujutsu sorcerers.
Due to the emergency nature,
three Jujutsu Tech first-years were dispatched to the scene,
and one died.
Juju Stroll
*Please ride in cars properly and safely.
Episode 4:
Curse Womb Must Die