Got you!
What's with that blood he spat out?
Acid?
What's this?
You're strong!
That's no fun.
Straw Doll Technique:
Resonance!
How many of them are there?
We should just keep going like it's whack-a-mole.
Yeah.
Keep going.
Keep exorcising them.
We'll crush every last one of them.
It probably won't retaliate.
You mean its main body can't attack since its technique covers a wide area?
Maybe. I'm not sure.
The technique's range, number of victims, the barrier,
and everything else we were worried about,
they all seem to be draining its main body.
We're in luck.
We should be able to exorcise it easily.
Which means, the real problem comes after that.
Kugisaki!
I'll be fine.
You just keep whacking that mole.
Damn it!
She gets sucked away so often!
But what was that just now?
The mole?
That earlier one?
Or something else entirely?!
Kugisaki?
Oh, hey, it's my big bro!
Me, too!
It ran away?!
Should I let it go?
Go after it!
Kugisaki and that thing both went outside the barrier!
She might be up against something much worse than we expected!
Handling things on this side won't be a problem!
I can handle this by myself!
Kugisaki is the priority!
Go!
If things go south,
you better come out too.
Why, you...
How dare you touch me!
A female?
Well, pardon me.
We brothers were tasked with an errand.
But killing sorcerers isn't part of it.
If you withdraw, we'll let you escape,
young lady.
An errand?
I assumed we were on the same errand.
Is this a cursed spirit? Or a curse user?
Which is it?
And what is that smell?
Last one!
Your sneak attack is too predictable.
Like I said, too predictable.
Was that all of them?
Tsumiki should be fine for now.
Next up is...
It's still alive?
That wasn't its main body just now?
The barrier hasn't collapsed either.
What's going on?
I shouldn't try too hard to find some kind of logic in a cursed spirit's actions.
But it's been bugging me this entire time.
Why did it start killing people it had marked only now?
The first cursed death was in June.
And in June...
Our objective here
is to retrieve Sukuna's finger.
Some have an overwhelming presence.
Some keep very quiet.
Some have already been consumed by a cursed spirit.
They're all resonating.
One of Sukuna's fingers was hiding inside a cursed spirit.
When Sukuna manifested within Itadori
back in June, it released its cursed energy.
It looks the same,
but compared to the one from the detention center,
it's much stronger!
Nue!
Okay, I win again.
This is unusual.
You rarely ask me to train you.
Are you in a rush after Yuji surpassed you?
Well, beggars can't be choosers.
Relying on me bothers you that much?
I don't think you're second to Yuji
when it comes to ability and potential.
The problem is just your mindset.
Megumi, you don't know
how to bring out your best, do you?
Excuse me?
Are you saying I'm not trying my best?
No, I'm saying you don't know how.
Look at the baseball game the other day.
Why did you go for a sacrifice bunt?
Did you want Nobara to advance the bases, even if it meant you'd be out?
Well, good for you.
But people like Yuji and me always swing for the fences.
I'm not saying a bunt is bad.
Baseball is a team sport, after all,
and everyone has their role to play.
But jujutsu sorcery is an individual sport.
Isn't it important to coordinate with other sorcerers?
Sure.
But no matter how many allies you have around you,
when you die, you die alone.
You're just underestimating yourself and the others.
You're not envisioning a stronger version of yourself.
Maybe because of that ace up your sleeve?
You think that in the worst case you can resolve everything at the cost of your life.
At that point, forget about me.
You won't even measure up to Nanami.
Winning by dying, and winning even if you die...
are two completely different things, Megumi.
Give it your all.
It's okay to be selfish!
How long was I out?
Was my Demon Dog destroyed?
No, the technique was released.
This is it for me, I guess.
Sacred Treasure: Eight-Handled...
What a waste of talent.
Fuck that!
A jujutsu sorcerer's growth curve
isn't necessarily a gentle slope.
Back then, why did you run away?
Bring forth the deepest of your shadows.
Worry about the specific structure later.
Just push out all the cursed energy you've focused.
Envision a future me who can freely surpass his limits!
Here we go!
With a strong foundation,
and a little bit of skill and imagination,
it just takes the slightest trigger to change a person.
Domain Expansion:
Chimera Shadow Garden!
It's incomplete!
It's hideous! How pathetic!
But for now, this will be enough!
Surpass the limits
of your imagination!
That is the interpretation
of my technique!
Demon Dog Totality's claws could even injure that.
Piercing through you is no big deal.
I'm tired.
Now, where are those guys?
Nice!
That's more like it!
There's one fundamental rule for interacting with others.
Do you know what that is?
I don't.
It's "I won't kill you, so please don't kill me either."
You can substitute "kill" with whatever you want.
The point is to agree not to violate the other person's dignity.
That is the rule which lets us acknowledge each other's existence.
You broke it and were arrogant enough to think you don't need it.
Must have felt really good, huh?
If I see you do it again, I'll kill you.
What did we ever do to you?
Figure it out on your own,
or go kill yourself.
Knock it off!
T-T-T-T-Today's the day I tell off Ikezawa and his buddies!
I won't be their lapdog anymore!
You've got this, Aida!
But I might become their next
punching bag, so don't try too hard, Aida!
Hey, come on, fatty!
Change of plans!
I'll tell them that you'll be the lapdog instead!
You'd sell your friend out, Aida?!
Shut it!
Megumi.
Huh?
Aren't those Ikezawa and his buddies piled up over there?
You said you wouldn't fight anymore.
Don't act like you're my guardian.
I hate bad people.
They have no brains and zero empathy, but they act like they're worth something.
I can't deal with good people.
They forgive the bad ones.
Then they view the act of forgiveness as a noble thing.
Makes me want to puke.
Tsumiki's the textbook example of a good person.
Disgusting.
Oh, sorry.
I didn't think it'd spill out.
When I was in first grade,
my father and Tsumiki's mother,
one parent each got hooked up
and then vanished without a trace.
Then this white-haired weirdo showed up.
So, about your dad...
He's actually from the Zenin Clan,
one of the biggest sorcerer families.
But he's such a loser, it freaks even me out!
He left the clan and had you just so he could use you.
You know, in your father's fight
against the Zenin clan, you're his trump card.
Pisses you off, doesn't it?
The money he left behind makes sense now.
Apparently, I was sold to this Zenin clan.
Yeah, it pisses me off.
Especially your lack of tact about it.
This irritating guy even wrote off my sale to the Zenin clan.
In exchange for me working as a sorcerer in the future,
we'd both receive financial support from Jujutsu Tech.
What's this sorcerer crap anyway? It's all bullshit.
Who the hell would I ever save?
Hey, Tsumiki!
What are you doing?
Megumi, ciao!
Nothing.
Hey, hold on.
So did you give any thought to the test of courage?
I don't really want to, but I'll tag along since I'm worried about you.
Shortly after I started ninth grade,
Tsumiki was cursed.
Identity unknown.
Origin unknown.
Multiple cases reported across the nation.
All we knew was that we didn't know anything,
and Tsumiki was left bedridden.
If I have the time to curse someone,
I'd rather spend it thinking about those precious to me.
Always smiling and spouting pretty ideals.
Not forgiving people isn't a bad thing.
That just shows that you care.
Even spinning my shortcomings in a positive light.
Yet she would genuinely get upset if I hurt someone.
That irritated me because I thought it was hypocritical in light of her leave-others-be policy.
Now I realize I had the wrong idea.
Just like how I choose who I save,
you chose to care for me.
I'm sorry.
I was too immature.
I'll apologize.
So just wake up already, stupid sister.
Crap, my head hurts...
This Yasohachi Bridge curse
was just overlapping the other one.
I doubt the curse that put
Tsumiki into a coma was undone.
Now, how do I break the news... to Itadori...
about the finger...
A huge presence just appeared.
Did the finger get out of the barrier?
If a sorcerer exorcised the finger's host,
they must be quite good.
Even if they did manage to defeat the special-grade,
there's no way they'd come out unscathed.
I hope they're okay.
My apologies.
Please forget what I just said.
Hold it!
He's going after the finger!
You and your way of running...
Do you really think you can get away like that?
I'm a bit insecure about my back, you see.
This is your warning.
If you see my back, I'll have to kill—
Oh?
Kugisaki!
Oh, brother!
You...
You saw it, didn't you?!
Sorry, brother! It wasn't on purpose!
Huh?! Who?! Sorry, I guess?
It wasn't on purpose!
I'll kill you!
Then what's with the get-up?
That's where this weird smell is coming from?
It gets stuffy!
Supreme Rot Technique: Wing King!
Death
by Wasp!
Juju Stroll.
Mr. Gojo!
Kugisaki!
Huh?
So annoying.
It's too hot for your craziness.
Fushiguro's getting hit on!
Formation B!
Roger!
Fushiguro, honey!
Who is that woman?!
Have you forgotten the night you toasted to my eyes?
You said I'm the only one who lights up your world!
Was that just a lie? Answer me!
That night! That night!
What?
Seriously, what the hell?
Could you not touch him so casually, please,
you homewreckers?!
It's time for Dear Megumi's violin practice with me.
Let's go home, my dear.
Today I'll have you master Twinkle Twinkle Little Star.
It's okay.
Don't mind them. Just go ahead.
The station's straight ahead.
Thank you so much.
Huh?
All right, seriously, what was that?
Could you stop? You're embarrassing me.
Explain!
Ow!