Are you all right, Inumaki?
Salmon.
Here it comes!
Stop!
Convergence: Piercing Blood!
He managed to wound it?
He wasn't serious at all when he fought me?
Hurry! It's just gonna heal right away!
Inumaki will stop it,
we will attack, and then retreat.
We'll keep this up until we get outside the veil
and rejoin with the principal and the others.
But there's no telling when the current balance will fall apart.
His cursed speech isn't affecting it much anyway,
and we're not getting a
chance to contact the teachers.
If it figures out how to deal with his cursed speech, we're finished.
Hurry!
The cursed spirit's objective remains a mystery.
There's a chance the principal
and the other sorcerers are immobilized.
Finding Todo is a priority.
Even Miwa would do at this point.
Inumaki will stop it.
Don't worry! Just go!
St—
He's hitting his limit first?!
Kamo! You still alive?
The cursed speech he used wasn't particularly strong, but it still destroyed his throat.
The enemy is just that much stronger!
Mustard leaf.
Inumaki...
That's enough!
Blast away!
You can't cut me with that dull blade.
Its eye branches are more fragile than the rest!
Now this sword isn't so bad.
I've got something even better.
This one feels disgusting to use, though.
Cursed tools.
Weapons which have curses imbued in them.
As with sorcerers, they're divided into grades
one through four based on their power and potency.
The higher the grade, the greater the advantage it provides in jujutsu combat.
Megumi, don't you dare lose that.
I won't.
If you sold it, you'd get at least five billion for it.
Wha—?
Special-grade cursed tool:
Playful Cloud!
Indeed, that is a good weapon.
Divine Dog.
With the exception of my
expanded technique, Bottomless Well,
if any of my cursed beasts get destroyed,
I can never manifest them again.
But the powers and techniques
of the destroyed beasts
get passed on to the next.
Totality!
It's fast.
It's going after my wounded arm first?
The sorcerer boy is in the forest...
The boy's sword!
Maki!
Don't ever make me use a
three-section staff again, please!
It's not cut out for me!
It's handy once you get—
Megumi!
Maki!
Damn it! All because I screwed up!
My strike was aimed at your heart.
You have incredibly quick reflexes.
Jujutsu sorcerers are extraordinarily compassionate.
They leave new openings every time their ally is hurt.
Is it destroyed?!
No, Megumi released the technique!
I wouldn't use cursed techniques if I were you.
The bud I planted in you loves cursed energy.
The more you use techniques,
the deeper its roots will extend into you.
How nice of you to warn me.
You're planning to kill us anyway.
I hear it's more effective when I explain it.
You move well.
But you're missing the edge you had earlier.
Wring out that cursed energy,
even if it rips you apart!
I'm not like the others.
I choose who I protect.
I bear the least responsibility!
That's why...
It's inexcusable that I be the first to go down!
Megumi, stop!
Our job here is done.
It's time to tag out.
You good to go, my friend?
Yeah!
So heavy!
I can't believe these two were beaten this badly.
It's up to you, Todo.
Your strength is the one thing you've got going for you.
Stop it, Itadori!
That's not something we can han—
Panda.
Yeah?
Take those two and exit the veil.
According to Nishimiya,
this is an anti-Gojo Satoru veil,
so the rest of us can go in and out no problem.
Wait! Even you can't—
Fushiguro.
It's okay.
Please.
Looks like you've realized it.
No one should interfere with those
who are about to spread their wings.
And that's exactly where Itadori stands right now.
If you die again, I'll kill you myself!
All right, let's go.
Pandash!
Can't afford to die now, I guess.
I won't lift a finger to help you, Itadori.
Not until you land a Black Flash.
If you can't land a Black Flash,
then I'll just watch you die,
no matter what happens to you.
Got it!
Sukuna's vessel... and who is that guy?
He certainly has an aura about him.
But judging by the amount of cursed energy,
he's undoubtedly weaker than me.
However, he has that mysterious brazenness.
He must have quite the technique.
I can't make any careless moves with him.
And what is this Black Flash?
So, what's your move?
You can talk?
There's something I want to ask you.
Are you allied with
a humanoid cursed spirit with a patchwork face?
And if I say I am?
He didn't carelessly close the distance.
I commend him for that.
He's fast!
He also has more explosive power than the girl earlier!
However, its intensity is disappointing.
Its torso's wide open!
It's underestimating me since I pulled my punches.
Now is my chance!
Black Flash!
Damn it!
My friend.
Anger is an important trigger for sorcerers.
People have been put to their knees
just because they provoked an inferior opponent.
However, it goes both ways.
Mishandling cursed energy when angered
wastes your skills, resulting in defeat.
Your friend was wounded, and worst of all,
they've rained on our bonding time as best friends.
So I understand better than anyone
why you'd be boiling with rage.
But that rage is too much for you!
Put it away for now.
Did they have a falling out?
All those distractions gone now?
Yeah, not a single one left.
Thank you so much, best friend!
Black Flash.
When an impact of cursed energy is applied within 0.000001 seconds of a physical hit,
a distortion in space is born.
The impact is equal to a normal hit to the power of 2.5.
No sorcerer can consistently use it at will.
However...
When comparing those who have experienced Black Flash to those who have not,
the gap between their understanding of
cursed energy is like that of Heaven and Earth.
What tremendous concentration.
The instant cursed energy impacts
within 0.000001 seconds of a physical hit,
space is distorted
and cursed energy flashes black!
Black Flash!
He's grown.
That was... Black Flash?
What the...
This is my cursed energy, right?
Now you've got the taste of cursed energy.
Up until now,
you've just been throwing together ingredients
that you weren't familiar with
and boiling them without knowing why.
But after experiencing Black Flash
and understanding the taste
of your ingredient—your cursed energy,
you now stand on a completely different level as a chef than you did three seconds ago.
Congratulations, brother.
You will become stronger.
I was told that Sukuna's vessel
was still inexperienced as a sorcerer,
but he and this mysterious guy...
Something about them is different from the rest.
It can heal itself?!
A cursed spirit's body is made up of cursed energy.
Unlike us, they don't need any
advanced reverse cursed technique to heal.
An injury like that is nothing to a special-grade.
However, there's no doubt that
it shaves away their cursed energy.
If we can crush its head, it's game-set.
Now, shall we get cooking?
It would seem that
I shall take you two somewhat seriously.
What a wide attack range!
Don't falter!
It sacrifices power and speed in exchange!
What a heavy hit!
It's not quite as heavy as that flashy black one,
but each of them is powerful enough to steadily damage me over time!
Todo! Let's sync up our timing better!
Gotcha!
Our footing!
I messed up!
Considering the amount of mass,
I thought it was manipulating
physical branches with its technique!
But it was all manifested from cursed energy!
That's a special-grade for you!
Let me teach you how to appreciate the land!
Attacking while we fall? That's brutal!
However...
Brother!
They dodged it?!
But what is this...
What is this feeling?!
You know, Hanami,
you should be more true to yourself.
I don't believe I'm faking anything.
I don't mean to call you a liar.
I know your reason for fighting.
But while we are fighting,
why not try to enjoy the battles—the present?
Do you enjoy them?
Well, yeah.
Though...
it was only recently that the joy and pleasure of battle became my main motive.
I was tricking, deceiving,
and murdering without a care.
And before I realized it, I felt fulfilled.
Just as humans eat, sleep, and screw,
I think this is a curse's primal instinct.
We might have gained the ability to reason,
but that doesn't mean we should deny our instincts.
The soul is a blend of instinct and reason.
No one has the right to tell you how to balance the two.
But your soul feels a little constrained.
I get the feeling that you're...
much stronger than you let on.
Ow...
Todo!
I'm perfectly fine!
It just used up a lot of cursed energy!
Now is our chance to strike!
You monster!
Mahito, right now...
I'm enjoying a fight!
You okay, brother?!
No problemo!
Excellent!
Then, it's time to unleash my technique!
Juju Stroll.
Coat rack!
Gonna make a sexy coat rack!
Hey, what kinda rack would Gojo Satoru be?
A standing coat rack, most likely.
I'd use his hip bone with the sacrum and coccyx as the base for the stand,
then rework his femurs to stabilize it.
For the newel post, I'd use his spine,
from lumbar up to the third cervical vertebrae.
To give it more height, let's see...
Ancient camphor wood would be good.
I could alternate its replicas with the bones to accentuate the height.
Then based on the overall balance,
I'd extend the spinous process and transverse process to create the hangers.
That'd be done by grafting on more ancient camphor.
Depending on the coloring, it might be
a good idea to cover the skull with tanned hide.
Nice! Very nice!
I'll make the best coat rack in the world!
No one needs it!