Tokyo
Jujutsu
High
School
Episode 21: Jujutsu Koshien
Curse
— One Day Prior —
*Principal Gakuganji's previous visit was to discuss
what items might be needed on the day of the event.
Baseball
Miwa Kasumi
Second Base
The mango she was letting ripen in the refrigerator is gone.
Nishimiya Momo
Outfielder
Baseball experience: 2L.
Kamo Noritoshi
Third batter
Practicing cursive. I can write my own name now.
Itadori Yuji
Catcher
First impression of iekei ramen: "I poop a lot the next day."
Kyoto
Tokyo
Kugisaki Nobara
Third Base
Awaiting approval for a credit card. Too hard for a high schooler, maybe?
Mechamaru
Zen'in Mai
First Base
Hated mangoes, but got over it recently.
Fushiguro Megumi
Outfielder
Prefers breast meat in chicken nanban and thigh meat in oyakodon.
Panda
First Base
Wants to punch a zebra someday.
Zen'in Maki
Pitcher
The one thing she can't tolerate is protein powder.
Mechamaru
Due to lack of players, one outfielder is permitted to use cursed techniques.
Kyoto
Tokyo
Todo Aoi
Catcher
Won the middle school nationals with Itadori. Itadori denies this.
Intentional
Inumaki Toge
Second Base
Prefers bread for breakfast. Likes it with ham, cheese, and a bit of tabasco.
Sister School Exchange Event
Second Day's Baseball Competition
Tokyo
Kyoto
30th Annual Exchange Event
Winner: Tokyo
Juju Stroll
Q: Rice or bread?
Q: Are you a rice person or a bread person?
Episode 22:
The Origin of Blind Obedience