I ended up not doing anything.
I wonder if they'll be mad.
Though in contrast,
you worked too hard.
Poor thing.
Shall I put you out of your misery?
Good work.
You're just a human. Don't act on your own.
Or I'll kill you.
Come on, I'm just being nice.
But I guess a curse wouldn't understand such subtleties.
So, got the goods?
Without a hitch.
All six of the special-grade "Sukuna's Finger" cursed objects
that Jujutsu High possessed...
and the other special-grade cursed object,
"Cursed Wombs: Death Paintings," One through Three.
Most of the temples at Jujutsu High
are actually just a facade.
Tengen's barrier keeps their position changing every day.
Among those, only one of over a thousand doors
leads to the storeroom
that holds cursed objects as dangerous as the fingers.
Only Tengen knows which door leads to the storehouse each day,
so I doubt anyone will interfere.
Who's Tengen?
A jujutsu sorcerer with an immortality technique.
Immortality?!
Who's stronger, him or Gojo Satoru?!
He has immortality, but not eternal youth.
You can think of him as just a tree.
Tengen basically doesn't interfere with the world,
aside from maintaining barriers.
You really don't have to worry about him.
Remember the finger we let Jujutsu High retrieve previously?
I placed a charm comprised of Mahito's cursed energy on it before they collected it.
It's under a single-layer seal, so they won't remove it.
He'll be able to find it easily.
Any gatekeepers?
There are two of Tengen's attendants between the door and the storeroom,
but they're chumps.
More importantly, before the veil goes down,
I'd like you to thin out the sorcerers standing by at Jujutsu High as quietly as possible.
We want to reduce the burden on Hanami.
Why aren't we sealing Gojo Satoru within the veil?
Because we don't want him to direct his attention toward Mahito's main mission.
And we need him to exercise a degree of his full power,
or it won't be a proper test of the veil.
Trapping the students inside will be more effective.
Is it okay to kill all but Sukuna's vessel?
That's fine, but I wouldn't recommend it.
Sukuna's actions
aren't quite what I had imagined.
This is just my guess,
but I believe one of the students
acts as a land mine for Sukuna.
If we step on that,
then in the worst case, all of our current plans will be ruined.
We should just kidnap Itadori ahead of time.
He's a pawn we'll be using anyway.
No, Itadori...
or rather, Sukuna himself, is also a bomb.
Both for us and for Jujutsu High.
We shouldn't agitate it until the moment we want more chaos:
October 31st, in Shibuya.
We should keep everything we can use to seal Gojo Satoru in reserve until then.
We'll have a few curse users accompany us, too,
but Kumiya Juzo...
He's disposable.
He's not the kind of person who can follow a plan all the way through.
He'll get in our way later.
We'll have a different human monitoring our commissioned test run of the veil,
so get along with them.
Hear that? Get along, Jogo!
Hmph!
I'm not going, anyway.
Come on, wake up, Hanami.
Let's go home.
Mahito.
Trying to pump the brakes on my hostility is incredibly stressful.
You're sounding more like a curse, too, Hanami.
Next up are the casualties.
Three second-grade sorcerers,
one semi-first-grade sorcerer,
five assistant supervisors,
and two cursed storehouse guards.
They're all sorcerers who were standing by at Jujutsu High
and working separately from Gojo and Principal Yaga.
We're waiting on the report from Ieiri,
but we're nearly certain it was the work of the cursed spirit
that Nanami encountered before.
Tsk.
Do you think we should share this information with the students and the other sorcerers?
No.
It's probably better to keep this among the higher-ups.
We don't want to give curse users certainty that special-grade objects were stolen.
Has the curse user we captured spilled anything?
It's not hard to get him to talk,
but most of what he says is irrelevant nonsense.
However, he claims that he only participated in the attack
because he was ordered to as part of a deal.
I wanted to make a coat rack.
That monk promised me that.
I don't know their name.
I couldn't tell if they were a man or woman.
Just a brat with white hair in a bob cut.
An androgynous monk kid with a bob cut?
That ring any bells?
Nope.
We sure he's not spouting bullshit?
Is there any sorcerer skilled at getting confessions?
How did a cursed spirit and outsiders
get through Tengen's barriers in the first place?
That was probably the work of the special-grade cursed spirit the students fought.
That one has a unique presence.
Even though it's a cursed spirit, it's incredibly close to a natural spirit.
According to Aoi, it was able to hide among plants.
And Tengen's barrier doesn't function against plants.
Tengen's barrier puts all its power into hiding, not protecting.
So once you get in, it's kind of weak.
Are they worried about Sukuna's Fingers enhancing Yuji's potential?
Or are they trying to enhance themselves?
Something isn't sitting right.
For now, let's be glad our students are safe.
But it goes without saying that the exchange event is now canceled.
Hold on.
That's not for us to decide, is it?
When did you start getting along with that gorilla?
Well, we got along, but like...
I remember what happened, but I wasn't exactly myself then...
What, were you drunk?
You believe I could've been drinking liquor in that situation?
I'm shocked.
But I'm glad you weren't seriously hurt, Fushiguro.
You're able to eat pizza now, too.
Come on, bring me something easier to digest.
No complaining.
Apparently, I got off easier because my cursed energy was all dried up.
Ieiri was still able to fix me up as soon as the roots were removed.
Huh, so that's a thing that can happen?
You fought against them, didn't you?
Itadori.
You've grown stronger.
Back then, we both said our convictions were proper ones.
I still think that's true.
Or, put another way, we're both wrong.
Huh?
Some questions don't have answers, you know.
You're thinking too hard.
You'll go bald.
That's right. There is no answer.
It's just whether or not you can accept it.
But there's no accepting anything if you can't have it your way.
Weak sorcerers can't do that.
So I'm going to become strong, too.
I'll surpass you in no time.
You never change.
Don't just move the conversation forward without me.
That's my brother's friends for you!
Where are you going, Brother?!
I'm grateful to you, but give me a break!
I wasn't thinking straight then!
What're you saying?!
We've been so close since middle school, Brother!
I didn't go to your middle school!
Hello! Useless Miwa here!
Even though I call myself useless,
I don't think I'm actually that bad.
But while everyone was risking their lives
fighting during the special-grade cursed spirit's attack,
I was fast asleep,
and now I feel ashamed.
Also, who broke my sword?
Was it Mai's older sister?
Between all that, we thought the exchange event was canceled,
but after taking a day off,
we're now...
Play ball!
...playing baseball.
So anyway,
a lot happened and some people died,
but how about it? Want to continue the exchange event?
I don't know what to say about it...
Obviously...
We're continuing it, of course.
T-Todo!
Your reasons?
First, only those with a connection to the dead have a right to mourn them.
It's not our place to butt in there.
And second, if people have died,
that's all the more reason we need to become stronger.
Acquired strength comes from the accumulation of results.
Tasting defeat and savoring victory
is what leads us to grow.
The most important part is for those results to exist.
Todo's surprisingly reliable.
Reliably crazy.
Third, when a student feels like they weren't able to bring out their best,
it hangs over them until they die.
How old are you?
I'm fine with that.
We'll win anyway.
It sounds stupid, but he has a point.
Why don't you rest, Kamo?
No objections here.
Salmon.
Will we draw lots for the individual battle pair-ups?
Huh?
There are no individual battles this year.
The exchange event has the principals of the Tokyo and Kyoto schools
each propose a form of competition to be held for an entire day over the course of two days.
But that's just how it is on paper.
Every year, the first day is team battles, and the second day is individual battles.
Salmon.
I hate routines, you know.
Every year, we put the competition methods in this box
and open it on the day of.
Principal Gakuganji's previous visit was to discuss
what items might be needed on the day of the event.
Baseball?!
You're here, too?!
What's going on here, Yaga?
No, I know I put individual battles in—
Get back here, Satoru!
Fly ball!
Nishimiya, don't run yet!
Out!
Huh? Why?
If you don't know the rules, then say so!
I know them! When the ball's hit, I run!
A sacrifice fly?!
What's that, some new form of torture?!
You're just plain stupid!
I heard you fended off a special-grade.
Huh?
Oh, yeah...
thanks to Todo and Gojo.
Don't you need a helmet?
Itadori, why are you a jujutsu sorcerer?
At first, it just kinda happened.
But I'm a lonely guy.
I want to save lots of people
and have lots of them watching over me when I die.
If you're not there, Mother,
I won't become a jujutsu sorcerer!
You have talent, Noritoshi.
You can save lots of people.
The more people you save,
the more you'll be recognized.
Then, in turn, all kinds of people will help you.
You'll only be alone for now.
One day, once you've become a great sorcerer,
come get me.
I see.
That's
a good
reason.
Strike!
Batter out!
Change up!
Kamo! You won't get a hit if you don't swing!
They call me the Mah of Tohoku.
No, Mah is the Mah of Tohoku.
Mah's a pitcher, you know!
Bonito flakes.
Huh?
Hold on!
Kugisaki's snapped!
It's a free-for-all!
That's obviously a pitching machine!
What are you talking about?
It's a spare. A spare Mechamaru.
We don't have a choice, since your Panda broke him the other day.
Pitching machine?
I don't understand.
You know a lot about machines.
Are you an otaku?
It's just one thing after another with you!
And yet somehow you're still a Jujutsu High student!
Fine, I'll do this!
Oh, she got on base.
She's desperate.
Out.
Tsk.
Okay, that's three.
That's cheating!
Bonito flakes!
Kugisaki, go back.
Catcher, huh?
Catching, throwing, leading, fielding, etc.
One could call it a fitting position for my brother.
But what I desire is a face-off with Pitcher Itadori.
Todo...
You could have been their pitcher.
He can't.
Mechamaru can't do anything but pitch right now.
Promise me, Brother.
If I hit a home run at bat this time,
next time you'll pi—
T-Todo!
Hang in there!
Nice pitch!
Maki, nice pitch!
Todo,
everyone
really hates you!
Do you still hate Itadori?
It's not a matter of liking or hating him.
Itadori isn't allowed to exist under jujutsu laws.
He's only alive due to Gojo's selfishness.
We must not bend the rules of the group for the individual.
Moreover, many others may die because Itadori lives.
But there are lives that were saved thanks to him, too.
Case in point, he worked together with Todo to fend off the special-grade.
This doesn't apply to just our students,
but they're going to stack up many regrets as time goes on.
"I wish I had done that."
"I wish they'd done this."
"I should have said that."
"I wish someone had told me this."
To be honest with you, I don't know what the right decision is with Itadori.
But for now, let's just watch over him.
Oh, he made it!
Inumaki's a fast runner.
Salted roe.
Mai! Miwa!
Watch for base-stealing!
We can save our regrets
for after that.
He nailed it.
Yeah!
Yaga, do something about Gojo first.
Juju Stroll.
Salmon.
Rice?
No, I like bread, too...
Wait, is it served with roe?
Rice.
Rice, I think?
What? I definitely prefer bread.
Salted rice ball.
Obviously bread, because I'm a panda!
You want me to kill you?!
This one's...
kind of forced...
They're out of ideas.
We're going home.