Operating Pro
1) Please
the room you wish to visit.
2) Please
confirm on the display.
3) Please
the room you're visiting.
Kanada Taichi in Morioka, in June.
Name: Kanada Taichi
Gender: Male
Date of Birth: February 10th, 1984 (34 years old)
Blood-type: A
Height: 175cm / Weight: 63kg
History: Saitama Prefecture, Saitama Municipal Urami
Elementary School. Same city, Urami East Middle School. After
graduation, he enrolled in the same city's Iwasa Commercial
High School. Dropped out in second year. Hired by Misaki
Construction, INC. Worked as an on-site laborer for two years,
then changed jobs. Moved to Morioka City, Iwate Prefecture.
Worked for Sakino Civil Engineering, LTC for four years.
Transferred to Soma Manufacturing Inc. and worked as on-site
laborer. Currently still listed as an on-site supervisor at the
same company. He was confirmed dead inside the entrance of
his apartment in Morioka City on June 23rd of this year, just past
8:00 PM. It's believed he was stabbed to death by a cursed spirit.
Right before his death, a resident witnessed Kanada shouting on
the phone after returning from his shopping.
Name: Shimada Osamu
Gender: Male
Date of Birth: July 27th, 1983 (35 years old)
Blood-type: AB
Height: 169cm / Weight: 74kg
History: Saitama Prefecture, Saitama Municipal Urami
Elementary School. Same city, Urami East Middle School. After
graduation, he enrolled in Shounan Private High School and
graduated. He spent two years working several part-time jobs
doing construction work, office work, and independent
contracts. Afterward he enrolled in Tongmyong University, and
after graduating he joined Rinne & Kidd Inc. He worked there as
a programmer for four years before transferring to SRAD'D Inc.
He worked there as a system engineer until the present. He was
confirmed dead in front of the entrance of his apartment in
Tsurumi Ward, Yokohama, on August 18th of this year, around
3:00 PM. It is suspected that he was stabbed to death by a cursed
spirit when he returned home from a nearby convenience store.
Shimada Osamu in Yokohama, in August.
Name: Yamato Hiroshi
Gender: Male
Date of Birth: October 9th, 1983 (35 years old)
Blood-type: B
Height: 180cm / Weight: 69kg
History: Saitama Prefecture, Saitama Municipal Yoha
Elementary School. Same city, Urami East Middle School. After
graduation, he enrolled in the same city's Urami High School and
graduated. He then advanced to Kanbe Commercial College.
After graduating, he joined Bereact Inc. One year later, he
transferred to Sangent Inc. After working there for three years,
he transferred to Houwa Home Inc. There, he worked in sales for
the Nagoya branch until the present. He was confirmed dead inside
the entrance of his apartment in Midori Ward, Nagoya, on
September 7th of this year, around 11:00 PM. It is believed that he
was stabbed to death by a cursed spirit upon returning from work.
Yamato Hiroshi in Nagoya, in September.
Jujutsu High Assistant Supervisor
Nitta Akari
Episode 22: The Origin of Blind Obedience
Spirit
Lantern
Morishita Family
Funeral 11:00~
Saitama Municipal
Urami East Middle School
Congratulations,
Making it to Koushien!
Grinding
Grinding...
Koi no Kuchi Canyon, Yasohachi Bridge
Spicy Cod Roe
Pounded Fish Cake is finally here!
Ding-ding
Gyaaah!
Bank ATM
Mugiwara
Open for business
Juju Stroll
Chinese Restaurant Manpuku
Episode 23:
The Origin of Blind Obedience - 2 -