Hey, are you listening?!
I told you! The auto-locking door was left wide open!
Don't make me repeat myself!
I told you this last week, too!
Why am I paying such high management fees?!
Huh?!
Screw you!
Do it today!
Come inspect it right now!
Are you even listening to me?!
I'll kill you!
These three died in similar circumstances.
They were stabbed to death by a cursed spirit at the entrances to their apartments,
and all of them had filed the same complaint
with the property managers several weeks before dying.
They claimed their auto-locking doors were left wide open.
None of the other residents have any idea what could have happened.
None of the dates or locations match, though.
Could the same cursed spirit have killed them all?
Hey, could the cursed spirit be responsible for the doors?
Do sensors like those pick up cursed spirits?
They don't show up on cameras and stuff, right?
Apparently, the cursed spirit made the door operators go crazy, not the sensors.
Oh...
Operators?
And as for whether or not the same cursed spirit was behind this...
Well, we couldn't be certain from just the residuals.
After all, a lot of time had already passed.
So we tried to track down any connections between the three.
We found that all three attended the same middle school for two years.
Meaning all three received the same curse,
and it activated after time had passed?
Precisely. That's highly likely.
So we're going to that middle school now
to question someone the three victims all knew,
and I want you three to see what you can find as sorcerers.
Way to go, Kugisaki!
Heh. What'd you expect?
A funeral?
Is this the home of that acquaintance?
Yes, it is...
Well, this sucks.
He died the same way the other three did.
Morishita
He lived with his family, so there was no auto-locking door,
but he was killed in front of the entrance.
Previously, upon returning home alone,
he reported, "The door was unlocked, but it wouldn't open,"
to his other family members.
I asked his parents, too,
but they said they didn't know what relationship he had with the other three.
Man, there goes our only lead!
Don't worry!
There has to be something at this middle school!
I sure hope so.
For now, I've secured an appointment with a teacher, so I'm counting on you.
Roger.
There's some obvious punks.
Let's beat 'em up and set 'em straight!
Why?
Huh?
I-It's good to see you!
Heh, look at that. You actually get it.
An aura just pours out, even if you try to hide it.
We haven't seen you since graduation, Fushiguro!
I... went here... for middle school.
That's a surprise, too, but that's not the point!
Look at me!
What'd you do?!
What did you do in middle school?!
No, it would be quicker to ask them!
Hey, Idiot A and Idiot B! What did this guy do to you?
We...
Or rather, every delinquent, gang member, and so on in this area
got beaten up by Fushiguro.
I beat them up.
Why do you keep talking so stiffly?!
Look at me!
What are you doing?!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Hey!
Who are you? Students from other schools aren't allowed in here!
And who the hell are you?!
He's clearly a staff member.
Why are you so combative?
We have permission to be here.
Oh, you're the ones?
You're all young.
You need to hang your pass around your neck.
Fushiguro?
Hello.
He remembers you!
So this man's been here a long time?
Probably.
Takeda's a permanent employee.
Then I leave the rest to you!
Abandoning her duty...
Kanada, Shimada, Yamato...
and Morishita, huh?
I was shocked by their passing,
but I guess it's been nearly twenty years since they graduated.
I remember it like it was yesterday.
They were problem children in their own right, though not as bad as you.
What did you want to know?
Strange rumors, dark rumors, connections to bad adults...
Hey, problem child!
...and anything of ill omen.
Dark rumors?
They may have been problem children,
but they never went beyond average middle school stuff.
But wait... ill omen?
Do you mean that tale?
About the Yasohachi Bridge bungee jumping?
You're still here, A and B?
Yasohachi Bridge?
A notorious suicide spot.
It's well-known in this area as a haunted location.
Oh, that's right! Back then, it was all the rage among delinquents
to bungee jump off Yasohachi Bridge late at night.
It was one of those tests of courage.
What a weird tribe.
I'm surprised there are people dumber than me!
What do you use for a cord?
We don't do it.
I just heard some students from our parents' generation talking about it.
One day, Kanada and the other three were absent without permission.
That wasn't all that unusual by itself, but when we contacted their families,
we learned that those four hadn't come home the day before.
It caused a pretty big stir.
Then they were found unconscious under the bridge.
They got chewed out good,
but all four swore up and down they didn't remember a thing.
I think that's it.
I've been to Yasohachi Bridge, too.
To bungee jump?
Ow!
It's easy for curses to take root in haunted locations, just like in schools,
so people from Jujutsu High regularly patrol it.
There wasn't anything unusual at the time, though.
It might be a bit famous,
but it's still used as a normal bridge.
We still have to go check it out, though.
Yeah.
Fushiguro?
Sorry, I was curious about something.
What is it?
Tsukimi took awfully good care of you when you were in school.
Is she doing well?
Yes.
Who's Tsumiki?
My older sister.
What?!
You tell us too little about yourself!
Yeah, that's right!
When they have cursed objects like these,
why don't they destroy them?
They can't destroy them.
Not when it comes to special-grades.
So they use a pact to put their life on pause and prevent harm to others,
preserving their existence.
Sukuna's fingers cause harm, though.
That's an exception.
It's a monster that still attracts curses over time,
even after becoming a cursed object and divided into twenty pieces.
And because of that, it can choose its vessel.
Hmm... Then anyone works for these?
Hey, you.
Money?
Money, right?
I don't have that much!
But there are loan sharks and stuff, right?!
Will he work okay?
He still can't see me, even at this point.
He's seriously lacking in ability.
Here, say "ahh."
We're here.
Koi no Kuchi Canyon, Yasohachi Bridge.
Once you confirm a cursed spirit's here, I'll lower a veil.
Roger!
Hey.
Sorry to ask this right after you woke up,
but could you go run a little errand for me?
Hey, we didn't find hide nor hair of any cursed spirit.
We didn't sense any presences or residuals.
I see.
Which means this isn't it. Guess it's back to square one.
But isn't it bad if we take too long?
Why?
Well, it's a famous haunted location, right?
There might still be plenty of others who got cursed.
And right now, the death rate's at 100%.
We don't want to see any others die, right?
True.
Ding-ding!
Bungee jumping was all the rage then, right?
So maybe the act of jumping off is the key?
Did she say "ding-ding"? Did she really say that?
She did! She did!
Itadori already tried that.
Huh?
What?! You mean you jumped with that vinyl cord?!
Hey, there you are!
Thank goodness!
Fushiguro!
Who's that again?
Fushiguro's underclassman.
Remember how much you picked on him?
You were talking about Yasohachi Bridge, so...
I'm really glad I found you here!
Fujinuma?
A classmate.
My older sister.
I'm glad you remember me.
I was talking to my sister about you yesterday, and...
Um, Morishita had a funeral in the neighborhood...
Then I heard from my brother that you were looking into that man and Yasohachi Bridge,
so I started wondering if they were related...
If what's related?
Morishita's death and the bridge...
They're not related.
We're just—
I...
I went there.
In eighth grade... I went to Yasohachi Bridge at night.
Geh.
Has anything odd happened at home recently?
Any strange feelings that only affect you and no one else?
My family runs a local branch shop...
and the shop's automatic door is wide open only when I come home.
Mom and Dad both say it's just a coincidence,
but there's definitely something there.
It scared me.
That's when I heard about you,
and remembered the Yasohachi Bridge.
When did the issue with your automatic door start?
It's happened about every other day for exactly one week now.
There's at least two weeks between when the four victims noticed something and their deaths.
We still have some time.
You didn't go to Yasohachi Bridge by yourself at the time, did you?
Do you remember who you went with?
Um, so this really does have something to do with...
Just with your automatic door.
But it has nothing to do with Morishita's death.
Fushiguro and the others are helping me with my college report.
"Electromagnetic Waves from Haunted Locations and their Effects on Electronics."
It's a huge pain in my gut!
But I want to hear from all kinds of people,
so I'd love to hear who you went with.
We'd better save her, after lying to her like this.
I went on a test of courage with two others from my club.
That's right. Fushiguro,
Tsumiki was with us then, too.
Tsumiki?
That's Fushiguro's sister!
I see.
Then I'll try asking Tsumiki, too.
Okay, then I'll escort these two home.
Please keep working on the report.
Something's up, isn't it?
I can't let you both go home on one bike!
Fushiguro.
Fushiguro!
Fushiguro, snap out of it.
Make sure she's safe first!
I'm fine.
Sorry, I'm stepping away for a sec.
I understand the situation.
A guard for Tsumiki, right?
But the only ones we have available right now are second-grade sorcerers.
Second-grade...
Since the number of victims far exceeds our estimates,
we'll have to re-evaluate the curse's grade, as well.
You were probably assigned to this mission with Itadori's growth taken into account,
so if it's even more dangerous than that,
it might be too much for a second-grade sorcerer.
It's just as dangerous for all of you, as well.
Personally, I recommend you withdraw.
What do I do?
Do I go back by myself right now?
No, the mission was already dangerous for all three of us.
I can't leave it to just the two of them.
Gojo will return next week.
I could ask him then...
No, I can't! The time limit is the big problem!
This isn't the type of cursed spirit that attacks someone.
It's the type that activates a cursed technique from within a marked person.
So there's no point staying nearby and protecting them!
I have to exorcise it right away!
Why were you talking to Ijichi?
Is your sister Tsumiki okay?
She's fine.
More importantly, this mission's danger level just shot up.
Other sorcerers will be taking over this case.
You two can go home now.
Huh? Why?
Us two? What about you?
I'll go back after I say farewell to Takeda.
Now go!
Thanks for your help.
Is this Nitta?
There's something I want to ask you.
The procedure, right?
Fujinuma didn't go over Yasohachi Bridge.
They held their test of courage under the bridge.
Itadori went under it, too.
Most likely, you can't get below it from up above.
The cursed spirit is within its barrier, so the procedure's important.
You go at night, from underneath.
And one more thing...
It's impossible to constantly keep a domain imbued with a technique deployed forever.
Which means it's like that barrier at the juvenile detention center...
an incomplete domain.
I'm actually lucky this time around,
since I won't need a veil.
You tell us too little about yourself.
Yeah.
You're seriously at your wits' end if you didn't notice us until now.
We're not saying you have to tell us everything,
but at least rely on us.
We're friends, aren't we?
Tsumiki's...
still bedridden.
The curse of Yasohachi Bridge only appears before its victims.
Since she can't communicate herself,
I have no idea when she'll be killed by the curse.
So I want to exorcise it right away.
But it's true that our mission's danger level has increased.
Okay, okay, we get it now.
You should have told us that from the start.
The cursed spirit is within its barrier, so the procedure's important.
You go at night, from underneath.
And one more thing...
At the bottom of the canyon,
there might be a river.
Crossing a river or other border— acts that symbolize crossing to the afterlife—
carry important meaning in sorcery.
There it is.
This one will be rewarding to exorcise.
What's this? Someone beat me here?
Huh?!
Fushiguro, this one's a different case, right?
Yeah.
Then you two focus on that other one.
I'll exorcise this one.
What?
You're going to play with me?
Juju Stroll.
Help! It's a purse snatcher!
I run a Chinese restaurant.
Allow me to treat you as thanks.
We couldn't!
Are you sure?!
Thank you so much! I'll gladly eat!
This restaurant has lasted four generations.
That was supposed to end with my father,
but I insisted and kept it running.
I wanted to keep this restaurant, this flavor, around.
What a nice story.
Sorry for the wait. Here's our pride and joy,
the gyoza meal passed down for generations!
Time to dig in!
Thank you for the meal!
You two...
What do you think of gyoza with no meat flavor,
that's basically just cabbage and thickener?
I'm glad you said something, Fushiguro!
She was a nice woman, too!
She was a nice woman, but still!
But apparently, gyoza is meant to be a vegetable dish, not a meat dish.
Seriously?