He was totally ogling my boobs!
Well, you do have a huge rack,
and they bounce when you run.
I get why you'd do it, Yoshino.
If there was a button
for killing the people I don't like,
I probably wouldn't be able to press it.
Gross!
But if there was a button
for killing everyone who didn't like me,
Pipe down, you guys.
I wouldn't hesitate.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
One adult for Human Earthworm 3.
That'll be 1,800 yen.
Yeah, here.
The show will be starting soon.
During the years I served as a doctor, saving lives,
And that brat had fifty-thousand on him!
I found myself arriving at this question again and again.
For real?
They're so annoying.
That's awesome!
Where does a person's life, their soul, actually reside?
So? What'd you do next?
High schoolers shouldn't skip school to watch movies.
I took it all, obviously.
Man, so mean!
Not that I can talk.
That's when I realized it!
Would it kill them to shut up?
The shape of one's soul creates the body!
Then today's your treat!
I can't hear the movie at all.
Fuck outta here.
So I began conducting research on the soul.
We're splitting it!
I guess people like them are everywhere.
All alone, in this lab deep in the mountains...
So, did you look?
I didn't.
Then are you saying Tsubasa's lying?
He was totally looking!
You're nuts, man!
Oh, there's a fifty-percent discount.
Huh? Where?
Hey! Teach him a lesson first!
Shit.
That girl is just using me to confirm her status.
You were looking, then.
Damn it.
I'm gonna say it!
You're not as cute as you think you are, Tsubasa.
These three know that too.
The only reason they're fawning over you is
because they think you'll let them bang—
Now to create the perfect human being!
It ain't happening.
She's not gonna let any of us bang her.
No point chasing after her.
Stop talking.
S-Stop it!
No!
It's Tsubasa.
Switch off your phone, damn it!
Hello?
What's up?
At this time? I'm free anytime.
Hey, guys.
Well...
Let's mind our manners, okay?
There's no need to worry. Everything went well.
It's all for the creation of the perfect human being.
Wha...
What is this?
Was it that guy?
There's no way a human could do that!
And if he actually did it, is he even human?
If I am the one who did it, what're you gonna do?
Judge me?
Were those guys important to you?
Don't worry.
You can eat it.
Harsh, man!
Poor guy! He's crying now!
Can I...
do that too?
Please stay back!
It seems like the victims were high school students.
Who were those guys?!
Why were they on the scene before forensics?!
One of them was just a kid, too!
I don't know the details either.
But you saw those stiffs, didn't you?
That's not natural.
Just pretend you never saw it.
Otherwise, you're looking at an early retirement.
Can you see it?
This is the residual taint of cursed energy.
Nope, I can't see anything—
That's because you're not trying to see it.
We typically see curses as if it's perfectly natural to.
When a cursed technique is used,
it leaves traces behind. That's what residuals are.
But residuals are much fainter than cursed spirits.
So please focus your vision and look closely.
Oh!
I can see them!
Of course you can.
Sensing them before seeing
is standard for one who is capable.
How about being little more encouraging?
I won't praise or insult you.
I adhere to facts and judge on that basis.
That is my way of doing things.
There was a time when I mistakenly believed that society operated the same way.
But that's a story for another time.
Let's follow the trace.
Yeah! Let's go all-out!
No, we'll use moderate effort if that is what's required.
Let's go.
We're just not clicking.
I'm not getting anything from him.
I won't be able to lead you this time.
But I've brought a reliable protege to take my place.
This is Nanami Kento,
the ex-salaryman jujutsu sorcerer!
Please don't.
We've got a fair share of weirdos in sorcery,
but since he is a former office worker,
he's got a good head on his shoulders.
He's a first-grade sorcerer, too!
That's rich coming from you.
Many of them like to wear sunglasses
and stuff to cover their eyes, huh?
Ex-salaryman?
Why didn't you become a sorcerer from the start?
Why don't we introduce ourselves?
Nice to meet you, Itadori.
Oh, right. Nice to meet you, too.
The one thing I learned at Jujutsu Tech
is that jujutsu sorcerers are idiots!
Whu?
Then I worked at your typical company, and I learned
that working is idiotic!
Really?!
If they're both equally idiotic,
I'll take the lesser of two evils.
That's the only reason I came back.
He's so gloomy.
Right?
Itadori, please don't think that
I'm of the same mindset as Gojo.
I do trust him and have faith in him.
But I do not respect him!
Say what?!
I'm not a fan of the way things are run,
but I follow the rules.
This conversation is dragging on.
In short, I don't acknowledge you as a sorcerer.
You might be carrying the bomb we know as Sukuna,
but please make an effort to prove that you are useful.
I'm weak and useless.
I've been getting that a lot these days.
But I'll get stronger.
I have to be strong,
or I won't be able to choose the way I die.
Even without that advice,
I'll make you acknowledge me.
Just give me a bit more time.
Be sure to tell that to the authorities, not me.
Oh, right.
Frankly, I couldn't care less!
Okay, I get it!
There wasn't anything on the surveillance cameras?
Right.
There was only one young man aside from the victims.
Then a cursed spirit was behind it?
Well, most likely.
There's a small chance
the young man could have done it,
but identifying him is the police's—
Lunch... Lunch... Lunch... Lunchbox!
Stop.
I'll take care of this one.
You handle the one over there.
Good... detergent!
If you feel you're in trouble, please let me know.
Have some faith in me, will you?
It's not a matter of faith.
I am an adult and you are a child.
I have an obligation to
prioritize your life over my own.
I'd rather be underestimated
than be treated like a child.
You've faced multiple life-or-death situations.
But that does not make you an adult.
Finding more and more fallen-out hairs on your pillow.
Your local store no longer having your favorite bread.
Experiencing little losses like these
is what makes people grow into adults.
My cursed technique forcibly creates a weak point on my opponent.
Seven to three.
When dividing the subject into tenths,
if I'm able to strike that point, it's a critical hit.
That allows me to inflict significant damage,
even on stronger adversaries.
If their cursed energy is weak,
I can cut them in two, even with this dull blade.
Are you listening, Itadori?
Huh?! You were talking to me?!
Ow...
Is it okay to reveal something like that?
It's not a problem to reveal that technique
to that particular opponent.
There's also the strategy of misleading by revealing.
I want to focus on the curse,
but it feels like I should be listening.
It does have its advantages.
Revealing one's hand is a pact that makes your technique more effective.
Like so.
That's all from me.
Wow.
Not only is his blade all wrapped up,
but he used the back of it and sliced right through.
Itadori, behind you.
Huh?
I don't like you looking away.
Who's the one distracting me here?!
Detergent!
Your cursed energy has a lag, huh?
Ow...
Lag?
Your cursed energy can't keep up with your explosive power.
Since you can't control it well, the trajectory is linear.
And that creates a unique flow of cursed energy.
The energy slams in right after you make contact.
In other words, one strike can equal two blows.
Divergent Fist!
That's so cool!
It doesn't come that easily for most.
This'll be a great weapon for you.
His physical strength is superhuman.
The initial blow has little cursed energy,
but it reaches 120% of an average sorcerer's power.
Then the real blow of cursed energy flows in.
It must be quite unpleasant to be on the receiving end.
He's got potential.
If he's able to go all out and combine
his full physical strength with a cursed technique...
I can see why Gojo brought him to me.
Box...
Apologies. Time to end this.
Itadori! Don't finish it off yet!
Have a look a this.
I took a photo of my opponent.
Wait, I thought cursed spirits didn't show up in photos.
Please stay calm and listen.
What we've been fighting...
They are humans.
No, I guess I should say they were humans.
The same as the three from the theater.
Their bodies were forcibly altered by a cursed technique.
If that was all, I would have noticed at the start.
The two we fought possessed cursed energy, like cursed spirits.
You'll have to ask the culprit
about their technique to explain that.
Though there is evidence that
their brain stems were tampered with.
Most likely to create a state of confusion and impaired consciousness.
If they can manipulate the brain, it might be possible for them to give cursed energy to humans.
The connection between the brain
and cursed energy is still a black box to us.
Oh, right, is Itadori listening?
Oh, yeah.
To sum it up, these guys died of shock
from having their bodies modified.
You didn't kill them.
Don't you dare think otherwise.
Right.
Either way, the gravity of death is the same to me.
But still, this...
This isn't right!
This kid genuinely gets upset over other people's deaths.
Those residuals were a bluff, likely meant to lure us in.
Our foe is quite skilled.
Looks like this will take more than moderate effort.
So let's go all-out.
Right!
There are spirits known as potential special-grade apparitions.
Cursed spirits are a culmination of
the cursed energy leaked from humans.
An image of fear shared by the masses can manifest as a powerful curse, even if it's not real.
An image of fear shared by the masses?
Like famous monsters and ghost?
Yup.
Like Toilet-bound Hanako,
the nine-tailed fox, and so on.
Sorcerers brand them as potential special-grade apparitions and keep an eye out for them.
The fact that they categorize powerful, unidentified curses as such really shows their shallowness.
But what people fear most aren't fairy tales, right?
So, natural disasters?
Talking to you is so easy.
Oh, r-really?
People have always feared...
the earth, the forests, and the oceans.
The cursed energy directed at them was so massive
that before they took form,
they gained consciousness and remained in hiding.
I'm proud to call them my friends.
What are you born from, Mahito?
People.
I am a curse born from the hatred and fear people hold in their gut toward each other.
I've organized the reports from our windows
on recent unnatural deaths and disappearances.
This should help us narrow down the culprit's hideout.
Aw yeah! Are we storming in?
No, this is just an approximation.
I'll continue to investigate this matter,
but I'd like you to handle a different task.
This is the boy who was at the theater, Yoshino Junpei.
Apparently, he goes to the same school as the victims.
Based on the surveillance footage and how he carried himself,
I believed it was unlikely he could be a curse user.
However, if he's related to the victims,
that changes things.
Curse user?
A jujutsu sorcerer with evil intent.
I've entrusted the process to Ijichi,
so I'd like you two to investigate Yoshino Junpei.
Roger!
Speaking of which,
I don't know any assistants other than you.
Well, I'm the only one who knows you're still alive, so by necessity...
Makes sense.
Let's go!
It's not just an approximation.
You already know the culprit's location, don't you?
Of course.
If they wanted to, they could have left the scene without leaving any residuals.
We're being lured in once again.
Weighing the risks of storming in alone
versus taking Itadori with me,
I simply chose the former.
He's still a child, after all.
Nanami Sir!
Itadori?
I forgot to say something.
Be careful, okay?
Itadori.
I'm not a teacher, so please drop the honorifics.
How about Nanamin?!
You want a smacking?
There he is.
Huh? He's not in uniform?
It looks like he hasn't attended school for some time.
We're walking from here.
Let's go.
Juju Stroll.
Nanami! Let's go out together!
No, thank you.
I mean, s-seriously!
I have something important to discuss.
Oh, how awful.
I haven't even said anything yet!