Woke up with a start
Warm tears in my eyes
Wanting to recapture the thread of my dream
Where can I find it?
I'm all alone
Please, give it back
Tell me when will I be free from this?
I will keep fighting
I'll keep enduring all the waves that come and go
Still lightheaded with sleep
I bury my face into the pillow
All I wish for is to have the same dream again
That wish takes my sleep away
I'm wide awake
Please, give it back
You are the only one for me
I can't remember your scent anymore
It's washed away by the waves
I'll go and grab hold of the rest of this dream, so wait for me
Before I realized, I got too attached to your kindness to be alone again
Should I try to lift my flushed face?
I want to believe that I'm not alone
I just want to believe
Give it a shot
In this ray of light that just dawned
I saw hope which made my chest all feverish
Hold my hand so we don't lose our way
So we can continue to walk the path we've chosen