Once again I woke up with warm tears in my eyes
Where are all those dreams I longed for?
Where are you?
I'm all alone
Please, give it back
Tell me when will it get easier?
I'll keep enduring all the waves that come and go
Still lightheaded with sleep, I bury my face into the pillow
All I wish for is to have that same dream again
That wish takes my sleep away, I'm wide awake
Please, give it back
You are the only one for me
I can't remember your scent anymore
It's being washed away by the waves
I'll go and grab hold of the rest of this dream, so wait for me
Before I realized it, I got too attached to your kindness to be alone again
Should I try to lift my flushed face?
I'm not alone
That's what I want
That's what I want to believe
Give it a shot
In this ray of light that just dawned
I saw hope, which made my chest all feverish
Take my hand so we don't get separated
Tomorrow, let's move forward on the path we've chosen for ourselves