Maki?
She's a weakling.
She can't even see curses.
Just a normie swinging around cursed tools.
She's forever a fourth-grade.
No idea why she's a sorcerer in the first place.
Break's over.
Okay!
I see.
That's a relief.
Mai, you idiot!
She's crazy strong!
She's using a long weapon.
I need to close the distance!
My hands are full just defending!
If she were using the blade,
I would've died twice already!
You call this a fourth-grade?!
She'd clean up second-grade curses no problem!
How is she swinging that polearm
in these cramped woods anyway?
New Shadow Style: Simple Domain!
My Simple Domain allows me to attack anything
within a 2.21-meter radius on full-auto reflex.
The technique is released if my feet
move from their position.
Not to mention, my Quick Draw is
most effective against head-on attacks.
It covers my blade with cursed energy
and accelerates the draw.
It's the fastest technique in the New Shadow Style.
But I doubt that'll be enough to settle the match.
I need to focus on creating an opening first.
Iaido? Looks like she's got some tricks.
Since I have the advantage of reach,
I bet she wants to knock away
my cursed tool to create an opening.
In that case...
She broke it?!
She's throwing away her advantage?!
She threw it!
A hidden weapon?!
Her intuition's sharp!
She's using decoys to close the gap!
My legs moved!
But that's okay.
I'll pull back and draw her in just close enough—
Aikido? She's skilled!
Huh?
Nice blade you've got here.
Sword-stealing?
Give it back?
What an interesting girl.
You should promote her to second grade already.
I feel the same way,
but the Zenin clan keeps butting in.
They should just be honest
and acknowledge her skills already.
I just can't understand connections that are not based on money.
I see you're being a cheapskate as always.
By the way, I can't help but notice that
the footage around Yuji keeps cutting out a lot.
Animals are fickle.
Sharing my senses with them is tiring, too.
Huh? Is that so?
Let's be blunt. Which side are you on, Mei?
Which side? I'm on money's side, of course.
There's no value to something that can't be bought.
You can't make money out of it, after all.
Just how much have you saved up?
I don't know what you guys are planning,
but it won't be so easy to deal with Yuji anymore.
Oh!
We got some action.
Charms are placed on curses released in the area.
When the curse is exorcised,
the corresponding charm here
in the viewing area is extinguished too.
They are extinguished in different ways based on the cursed energy registered.
When the Tokyo school exorcises one, they burn red.
When the Kyoto school exorcises one, they burn blue.
Since Maki is participating, we've made sure any unregistered responses burn red as well.
All these one-on-ones...
Did they forget why it's called a team battle?
Why can't they just get along?
They must take after you, Utahime.
You're the only one I have an issue with!
By the way, Panda is the one who exorcised it.
Lucky me!
Get down here, you damn witch!
I've come down a few times already.
Gonna catch me or not, rookie?
Her cursed energy wind
is strong enough to blow me away!
These pebbles and branches hurt like hell!
If I drop my guard, it'll rip me to shreds!
How dare you hurt my precious face?
A scar on the face is a badge of honor for a man.
Though it's only a flaw on a woman.
Say what?
You think the world of sorcery is all about skill?
And it actually is.
That only applies to men.
Uh?
Even if a girl is skilled,
if she's not cute, she's looked down upon.
Of course, it's the same
even if she's cute but lacks skill.
Do you get it?
It's not just strength they demand from female sorcerers.
They demand perfection!
And on top of that,
Mai has to deal with even more outrageous demands.
Yeah, I get it.
I get that you're a pain in the ass!
She's only a first-year
and she's already used to fighting?
She gets back up no matter
how many times I knock her down.
I've gotten used to being tossed around.
If I up my output any further, I might kill her.
No, that's really just an excuse.
The main reason I can't attack her is Inumaki.
Cursed Speech involves
infusing sound with cursed energy.
You just need to protect yourself
with cursed energy from ears to the brain.
The technique is specialized for use against curses.
Like I said, it's nothing to be afraid of
if you know it's coming.
On the contrary, if you're not sure if it's coming,
you're constantly distracted.
Protecting the inside of your head is difficult enough as it is already...
He's such a nuisance no matter where he is!
All done with your lecture?!
Perfection is easy compared
to what is demanded of Mai!
As one of the elite sorcerer families—
one of the Three Great Clans—
perfection is but the norm for the Zenin clan.
"Inherit the Zenin clan's hereditary technique."
Any who don't meet that demand start their sorcerer lives as failures.
Among those, women aren't even allowed to stand at the starting line.
Without the Zenin clan lineage,
they're not considered sorcerers.
And if they're not sorcerers,
they're not considered people.
She has lived her entire life being despised in a family without a shred of affection.
Can you imagine the hardships Mai and the others go through just to enjoy what we take for granted?
Why don't you try thinking that over
with that brain of yours
which confuses curses for friends.
Shut up already.
You think misfortune is a free pass to do anything?
What, then?
You're okay with the fortunate
getting trash-talked behind their backs?
It's what drove Saori away...
I can't stand Mai regardless of her upbringing.
And I love Maki who endured the same thing.
Have any of you ever stopped to consider
what kind of person the idiot you're trying to kill is?
What makes us obligated
to meet such absurd demands?
Is your entire life just a job?!
Straw Doll Technique:
Hairpin!
So that's why she kept shooting nails
that didn't land any hits?!
You might have brought me lower, but you still won't reach me!
Nope, I got ya!
This is plenty!
My broom's bristle? She must've grabbed it just now.
I don't give a damn about "men" this and "women" that!
You can keep that shit to yourselves!
I love myself when I'm pretty and all dressed up!
And I love myself when I'm kicking ass!
I am...
Kugisaki Nobara!
I can't control my broom!
If I hit her with my hammer, I might end up killing her.
Which is why...
A squeaky hammer?!
One more time!
Just barely within effective range.
Great. It hit its mark.
Hello? Momo?
Don't worry, it's just a rubber bullet.
More importantly, that light
earlier was Ultimate Cannon, right?
And now I can't get in touch with Mechamaru.
That's not a good sign
after he was forced to use that.
It's safe to assume he's out.
Panda will most likely be back.
Get away from there and
support everyone from above.
We're all in trouble without you.
Okay.
Mai, I...
It's all right, Momo. I know.
Yeah.
What, not gonna call your friends?
I don't mind going two-on-one.
There are many ways to enjoy this, don't you think?
I could have everyone beat you up together,
but I'd like to enjoy you...
all by myself.
How about treating me with some respect, kiddo.
What do you think of Maki?
She'll be mad no matter what I say!
I-I think she's a very wonderful lady.
What? I mean as a sorcerer.
Oh, that? Thank goodness!
Honestly, I still don't know much
about sorcery and all,
but I can tell she's a fighter.
It's obvious from the way she carries herself.
Maki is only a fourth-grade.
Wait, really?
Her family is an annoying clan of sorcerers.
After she basically expelled herself and left, they've been interfering with her promotion.
If they're a powerful sorcerer family,
why wouldn't they want someone that strong?
They won't acknowledge
what they've already rejected.
'Cause they're idiots.
But if she performs well at the exchange event and her name gets spread around,
it'll be harder for them to harass her like that.
So let's start by winning the team battle!
Fight like you're gonna die again!
Sure.
I can hear you.
Jeez.
I shouldn't let myself get distracted.
What are you smiling about?!
You think you can stay in my blind spot forever?
You'd have to be an idiot
to try and put distance between us.
From below?!
I knew it already.
Maki has a talent that I don't.
Have you heard about Ogi's daughters?
One can't even see curses, let alone use techniques.
Twins are a sign of ill fortune, after all.
Maybe it's better this way.
All they'll have to do is serve the eldest son.
Mai.
What's the matter? Hurry up.
I don't wanna.
What's the problem?
We'll get in trouble again if we're late.
Something's there...
Again?
All right, fine.
Anyone ho... home...
Come now, close your eyes.
If you can't see it,
it's like it's not even there.
You've always been so fearless.
Always plowed forward toward the future.
I hated you.
You're leaving the clan, Maki?
You have plenty of servants, right?
Don't worry, though.
I'll be back someday, Clan Leader.
What for?
To become the head of the Zenin clan!
Then I shall put you through
ordeals befitting that ambition!
Do as you please.
And Mai, as well.
She has nothing to do with this.
Liar.
I hate you!
That's six shots!
I won't let you reload!
I hate you!
That's why
I never told you about things like my first crush
or my cursed technique!
Construction.
A technique that creates matter from cursed energy.
Unlike creating objects within
the barrier of a Domain Expansion,
the matter produced by Construction
doesn't disappear when the technique ends.
However, it consumes a lot of cursed energy
and puts heavy strain on the body.
Creating one bullet a day is Mai's limit.
That's why she uses a revolver to fake her bullet count.
I win.
She caught the bullet?
Ow!
I shouldn't touch that with my bare hands.
Maki has a talent that I don't.
It's like the opposite of
Mechamaru's Heavenly Restriction.
You were supposed to be born with a cursed technique,
but you traded it for superhuman physical abilities.
The Zenin clan wouldn't acknowledge it.
That talent I lacked.
That's game, set, and match. Wouldn't you say?
Why did you leave?
Why? Do I have to spell it out?
You joined Jujutsu Tech yourself!
I never wanted to!
I never wanted to be a jujutsu sorcerer!
It's all your fault!
Always trying your hardest!
Forcing me to do the same!
All this effort, pain, and fear. I've had enough!
What was so bad about
being ordered around back home?!
We could've just done a few chores
and lived a normal life!
Why wouldn't you fall down the hole with me?
Because I would have hated myself if I did.
That's all there is to it.
I'm sorry.
Maki, don't let go!
I won't.
Promise?
Jeez, give it a rest.
Promise me you'll never leave me behind.
Of course I won't.
We're sisters!
You lied to me.
I hate you so much.
Juju Stroll.
I need food.
If I recall correctly,
I kept leftover soybeans from lunch in the...
Sorry.
At least try to look a little sincere, will you?
Here, have this and we'll call it even.
Nah, I'm not into late-night cup ramen.
How about this?!
Nishimiya-style Seafood Cup Ramen recipe!
First, chop up hot chili peppers using scissors into the seafood cup ramen!
Then, fill the container halfway with milk.
Finally, add hot water up to the line inside!
Since we're using milk,
make sure the water's boiling hot!
I-It's delicious!
This is really good!
Right?
Maybe I'll try it next time, too.
You could've just eaten this if it's so good.
Well, you still pay for
late-night cup ramen the next day.