Back in third grade,
I beat up a cocky high schooler.
Even if he was older, cocky is still cocky.
He mocked me.
And when I feel like I'm being mocked,
that's when the gong rings on the fight.
It wasn't that fun.
Trouncing a boring guy was naturally boring too.
Nice fight, boy!
What type of girls do you like?
Who are you?
I had a feeling that my boredom
was about to be flipped upside-down.
It's time to unleash my technique!
Huh? Didn't you use it before?
However! I have no time to explain my technique!
So I've got only one thing to say.
Don't stop!
Believe in me!
Okay! That's two, though!
Let's analyze our opponent's cards.
There are roots that emerge from the ground.
That one probably gains power and speed the more it limits quantity and range.
Then there's Wooden Ball.
Each ball can attack once or twice, and then it's expended.
They can remain airborne, and I have to watch for delayed activation.
Then there's Cursed Bud.
That's probably what Fushiguro got hit with.
Is it game over with just one hit?
Hopefully it can't fire too many of them.
Then there's Flower Field.
It's supposed to get your guard down,
but its injuries are affecting this ability.
Nothing to be afraid of.
Then there's that unleashed left arm.
There's also the possibility
that all of these are just bluffs!
However, it doesn't matter what a technique is
if you don't let them activate it!
Even accounting for any unexpected situations thanks to my 530,000 IQ,
my galaxy-brain CPU produces only one conclusion:
Victory!
Because I'm not alone,
Brother!
Because you're here!
Todo!
That's one down.
Oh, Todo!
I see.
It's simple...
and therefore a troublesome technique.
Yeah.
My technique swaps my position with my opponent's.
Boogie Woogie!
Todo!
Shh! We'll end this before it gets used to it.
By the way,
clapping my hands
is the trigger to activate it!
Their builds are too different!
There's a big difference after they swap!
Is he swapping with me?
Or is he swapping with Sukuna's vessel?
Every time he claps, that split decision makes my thoughts falter!
This isn't good! I can't...
...break out of this!
They're using that again!
Using Black Flash consecutively isn't anything amazing.
Using it more than twice in a row,
or on the same day might be difficult.
It doesn't matter if the first time was pure luck or skill.
Once they land a Black Flash, sorcerers temporarily enter a state athletes call "the zone."
The otherwise conscious manipulation of cursed energy becomes as natural as breathing.
There's a sense of omnipotence,
as if everything else revolves around them.
That might be a good way to put it.
My record?
Four times.
I just got lucky.
Black Flash!
Brother,
I always get that premonition from you...
Black Flash!
Three in a row!
Don't get cocky!
Swapping positions?!
What I have to be wary of right now
is Sukuna's...
They didn't swap?!
A clap doesn't necessarily mean I'm activating my technique!
It's a simple but effective trick, wouldn't you say?
...I'm getting that same premonition of my boredom being turned upside-down!
Black Flash!
It's attacking before each swap!
It's getting used to Todo's technique!
But that Black Flash barrage definitely did some damage.
We can exorcise it!
Together!
This is the first time I've ever been hurt so badly,
and despite that...
the thrill of this battle isn't waning!
His technique reveal was full of lies!
He can make others swap places as well!
Todo!
He's protecting me!
Not to worry, Brother!
By using everything I've got
to harden my body and cursed energy,
I'll easily repel these buds!
Are you sure about that?
T-Takada?!
You remember Fushiguro's injuries?
Of course I do!
Those are the same cursed buds that are coming for me as we speak!
That's why I'm—
But remember,
Fushiguro's buds had grown a little.
You think it grew by sucking his blood?
Sure, that's one possibility.
But the opponent is a cursed spirit.
What do you think is more likely?
Cursed energy!
He dispelled his cursed energy at the last moment!
He figured it out?!
The harder they defend with cursed energy,
the stronger those buds become!
Her next one's the national?
I'll have to thank her then,
won't I?
Hey, special-grade,
I know you've realized I didn't tell you the whole truth.
But there's one more thing you need to think about:
What counts as a target for Boogie Woogie!
What can I swap within the range of my technique?
Only living things?
Non!
My technique works on cursed corpses
and inanimate objects as well.
So, the answer is:
anything that possesses
cursed energy above a certain level!
Hey, special-grade, have you noticed?
We're back at that spot again.
This is where it lies waiting!
Maki's special-grade cursed tool is in the riverbed.
The branches on its are face are especially fragile.
The river?!
What did I even swap places with?
Special-grade cursed tool,
Playful Cloud!
Even a blow from a special-grade cursed tool imbued with my cursed energy wasn't enough?
Plants do not generate cursed energy.
So my left arm steals the life from plants and converts it to cursed energy.
But that energy never comes to me.
It all goes to this flower offering.
I would've liked to avoid using this.
Todo!
Stay away, Brother!
It's gonna be an incredible blast of cursed energy!
However, you'll easily avoid it with your technique.
So what shall I do?
Domain Ex—
The veil?!
I see.
I thought he sounded pretty good without the amp,
but this geezer is the amp himself.
His technique amplifies the tune
he plays and launches it as cursed energy.
He's a predictable mid-range fighter.
He obviously doesn't want people closing in on him.
I'll make a wallet out of you!
One infused with the essence of old man stink!
Roger that.
Nishimiya, you keep going too, and head to Shoko.
It's okay.
Mei has eyes on Miwa.
Thank goodness we still have reception.
Guess that makes sense, given the effect of the veil.
Someone at Jujutsu Tech is working
with a curse user or maybe a cursed spirit.
Looks like he wasn't mistaken.
Huh?
I thought I cut you for sure.
A human?
The curse user?!
There I go again...
It's nice, isn't it?
Juzo made it for me.
Didn't you run into him earlier?
You're weak, so even your
sword will hold your hand.
...he said.
So, what are you gonna give me, lady?
I bet you're not popular with the ladies!
You meet someone new,
and all you talk about is yourself.
I'd charge you for this.
What makes you think you're a good enough listener to charge for it?
You guys!
Shut up! This isn't the time to be picking fights!
Wow! So many girls!
I'm so popular!
Are you even listening?
I'll back you up. Just make sure you
don't get caught in some friendly fire.
You better be careful not to hit me!
The veil is gone?!
For real?
Has it even been thirty minutes?
Time to run!
What was his deal?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I can see that slick coat rack!
Well, then.
Where should I start?
Huh?
Looks like this is as far as we go.
Huh? Mr. Gojo?!
Yuji is on a much higher level than before.
I see, Aoi!
Of course he'd be a great match for Yuji.
Looks like they're fighting the special-grade,
but I shouldn't have to worry about them.
In that case, let's start with...
You.
Rack! Rack! Rack!
Don't kill him!
We have a lot to ask this guy.
Don't let him die on us.
Go on, treat him.
The guy near Utahime disappeared.
Seems that running away
was an option from the start.
All that's left is that one?
Also good at running away.
Yuji and the others are a little far away.
Oh, well.
Guess I'll be a little rough.
Cursed Technique Amplification: Blue.
Cursed Technique Reversal: Red.
I'm withdrawing.
I'm not arrogant enough to face Gojo Satoru.
Don't you dare!
What were you all trying to do here?!
Hold it, Brother!
Why are you stopping me, Todo?!
Don't take another step forward.
Or you'll get caught in it.
Hollow...
Purple!
He's just as nonstandard as ever.
I can't tell if it was exorcised or not.
Ow! It hurts!
Quiet!
Yay!
That settles everything!
Or, I guess it doesn't.
I wonder if Hanami is okay.
Mission accomplished.
Juju Stroll.
Salmon!
Dog?
No, maybe cat?
Wait, maybe dog if it's a big dog!
Dog.
Dog, I think?
What? I'd definitely go for cats.
Salmon.
The answer's obviously pandas!
You got a death wish?! Huh?!
Everyone hates me,
don't they?
Well, there were only two choices.
Just leave him be.