Morning.
So which one are you right now?
Aren't you...
Gojo Satoru.
I teach first-years at Jujutsu Tech.
Jujutsu?
Fushiguro...
My friends!
What the hell is this?
I'm not sure you should be worrying about others,
Itadori Yuji.
It's been decided that you are to be secretly executed.
Hello, Sugisawa Hospital.
Oh, this is Itadori.
I just called earlier.
Yes.
Yeah.
I'm sorry to keep calling but,
how is my grandpa doing?
Huh? I thought they already told you.
Oh, please hold on. I'll go ask myself.
Mr. Itadori never uses his call button.
It's actually scary that he doesn't.
Mr. Itadori, you have a phone call.
Yuji is asking if you want him to bring any—
Leave me alone!
Tell him not to come!
He should go to his club! His club!
What? What's going on?
Well, you heard him.
What club are you in, Yuji?
Yeah, I heard.
I'll come by tomorrow evening.
They're keeping a cursed object in a place like this?
Could they be any more stupid?
There's nothing here.
Huh?
The Stevenson screen's empty.
For real? That's hilarious!
Maybe it took a nighttime stroll.
I'm gonna punch you.
Well, no going home until it's recovered, okay?
I'm gonna hit him for real this time.
It's about time.
Are we really doing this?
Sasaki?
Iguchi?
Okay, here we go!
Spirits, spirits, please tell us!
Which creature is the council president afraid of?!
Sea Butterfly?
A sea butterfly? That's so lame!
What a small fry!
Occult club!
Hey, it's the Plankton President! What's up?
As you were previously informed,
a research club with no real activities must forfeit its club room.
So vacate this room at once!
You really shouldn't underestimate our members, President.
What's that?
You know about our rugby field being closed off, right?
Yeah, some of the students who got sick actually had to be hospitalized.
Don't you think that's strange?
We're talking about tough rugby players here.
Truth is that just before they started feeling sick,
they heard mysterious sounds and voices coming from the field.
That's when we found this newspaper article from thirty years ago.
It talks about the disappearance of a construction worker named Mr. Yoshida.
He was last sighted here at Sugisawa Third
High School during its construction.
Mr. Yoshida was struggling to make ends meet,
so he turned to loan sharks
and those organizations were after him.
Which means!
The commotion was caused by Mr. Yoshida's
vengeful spirit who's buried at the rugby field!
No, actually it was just ticks.
Hard ticks.
A large, blood-sucking bug.
It can be fatal if it bites you and infects you with SFTS,
so be very careful.
So what?!
The occult club is uncovering occult activity,
so it's still a proper activity report!
This isn't some kid's game!
Besides, the problem here is you, Itadori Yuji!
You're registered with
track and field, not the occult club.
So this club doesn't even have
the three members required to be a club!
Wha—
Itadori
No, I'm sure I wrote down the occult club.
I rewrote it!
The track and field coach, Takagi?!
Itadori, we need you for conquering the nationals!
Here's a teacher more problematic than the students.
Give it a break!
How many times do I have to refuse?
No can do!
Why not?!
However, I'm not some monster.
If you can beat me, I'll give up on you.
Let's settle it fair and square on the track!
Now that's interesting!
You're on!
How fair and square is it
to rewrite a student's club application?
Something's off about this rugby field.
Is there a dead body buried here or something?
Even if there is,
I'm surprised to see one this high-leveled.
That's probably a second-grade curse.
Must be that cursed object's influence.
Damn it.
Its presence is too big to pin down.
It feels like it's close but it could still be far away.
This special-grade cursed object is a serious pain.
Who could have moved it?
Where is it now?
Check this out!
Coach Takagi is taking on Itadori from West Middle!
Whoa, what are they competing in?
Hell yeah!
Fourteen meters!
Wow, Takagi's still got it!
Itadori! Itadori!
What're you gonna do, Itadori?!
Hey, is Itadori famous or something?
They're probably tall tales,
but I heard he beat all stages of Ninja Warrior,
and that he's the reincarnation of Mirko Cro Cop.
But Mirko's not even dead yet.
He earned the nickname "Tiger of West Middle."
Lame.
Hey, can I just throw this however I want?
Yep. I won't call any fouls,
so throw however you please.
I'm sorry, I chose something that isn't your forte.
Hopefully this will show you how serious—
Uh, roughly thirty meters.
All right, I killed it!
Tiger? More like, Gorilla.
That was a pitcher's throw.
Itadori, you'd do well on a sports team.
You don't have to force yourself to stay in our occult club, y'know?
Huh?
But as much as you two love scary things,
you couldn't go to haunted places without me, could you?
We're scared because we like it.
Yay!
Besides, everyone in school has to be in some club, right?
I could never keep this up.
You don't have to do anything!
You can be a ghost member!
We're the occult club, after all!
I did say that.
I've got my reasons, and I need to be home by five.
So if it's okay with you, I'd like to stay.
The occult club is really growing on me.
Well, suit yourself. We don't mind.
Yeah.
That guy's incredible.
He pulled that off without any cursed energy.
I wonder if he's like Zenin.
Crap, it's already half past four!
Later, Coach. I've got stuff to do!
The presence of a cursed object!
Hey, you!
How the heck is he so fast!
I heard he runs the fifty meter dash in three seconds.
What is he, a car?
I told you not to come.
Don't be buying flowers all the time.
You always give me that.
Besides, these aren't for you. They're for the nurses.
All the more reason not to, you goof!
And what happened to your club?
Why aren't you at your club?!
Oh, chill out.
It ends before five.
I wouldn't have come here if I wasn't so bored.
Good.
Since you've got free time,
listen to what I've gotta say.
Not interested.
Just listen anyway.
I have some final words for you.
It's about your parents.
As I said,
I'm not interested.
Grandpa, could you stop
trying to act all cool before you die?
A man wants to go out in style, y'know!
Get a clue, you idiot grandson!
Quit snapping over everything.
You can just be yourself.
Tch. You've had it too easy.
Yuji.
Hm?
You're a strong kid, so help people.
It doesn't have to be all the time, just whenever you can.
It's okay if you feel lost.
Don't expect gratitude in return.
Just save as many as you can, even if it's just one.
When it's your time to go,
make sure you're surrounded by people.
Don't end up like me.
Grandpa?
Yes, what's the matter?
Hello?
Mr. Itadori?!
My grandpa... is dead.
Okay.
That's all of the necessary paperwork.
Okay. Thank you for everything.
Are you sure you're okay?
Well, this is my first time experiencing
something like this so it hasn't really sunk in yet.
But Grandpa would snap if I kept moping around forever.
So I'll just have to laugh as I roast him up.
Phrasing!
Itadori Yuji, right?
I'm Fushiguro from Jujutsu Tech.
I'd like to have a word with you.
Right now.
Um, I'm in mourning right now.
Sorry, but there's no time.
The cursed object you have is extremely dangerous.
Hand it over to me right now.
Cursed object?
This.
Oh, yeah, yeah. I found that.
I don't really mind giving it back,
but my friends were totally into it.
What do you mean, dangerous?
Nationally, the average number of unexplained deaths and missing persons exceeds ten-thousand every year.
Most of them are a result of curses.
Curses?
It doesn't matter if you believe me or not.
Those are the facts.
Moving on.
Crowded places like schools or hospitals are likely to form pools of negative energy.
Hardship, regret, humiliation.
Mankind's negative emotions become the source of curses.
That's why a cursed object is kept at such places as a protective talisman.
The object you found is one of them.
If it's protecting us, shouldn't we be grateful for it?
Let me finish.
A cursed object of greater evil is said to be a deadly poison that keeps lesser curses away.
In reality, it's a bad practice that only claims to protect.
Over the years, its seal weakens and
it starts to attract curses which try to feed on it.
The object you found is a dangerous one,
classified as special-grade.
Hand it over before people start dying.
Hey, I already told you I don't mind.
Explain it to my friends.
It's empty?
I was just chasing the
cursed energy lingering in the box?!
Where are the contents?!
Like I said, my friends have it...
What is it?
Actually, they mentioned something
about peeling off the seal tonight at school.
What? Is that a bad idea?
Bad doesn't even begin to describe it.
They're gonna die.
I can't get it off.
Did we really need to sneak in to do this?
I'm turning on the lights.
No! The atmosphere's important!
Enjoying the thrill is the spirit of the occult club!
It's not like anything's gonna happen, anyway.
Oh, it came off!
A human finger?
Is it real?
Is this...
What is this?
Do seals come off that easily?
No, it's impossible for people who lack cursed energy.
Normally.
Go right! It's a shortcut!
This time the object itself is too strong.
That ancient seal might as well be normal paper.
I still don't get all this stuff about curses.
Where are they?
Fourth floor!
What is this pressure?
You stay here.
I'm coming, too!
It's dangerous, right?
I've only known them a few months,
but they're my friends. I can't just stand by!
Stay here.
What time is it?
The hour hand is at eleven.
What is that monster?
S-Sasaki...
Iguchi? Thank goodness! Where have you—
Help me...
What time is it?
The curse has been unleashed!
Its presence is all over the place!
Out of my way!
Demon Dogs!
Go and feast.
Am I just going to wait here like he told me to?
What am I so afraid of?
They're gonna die.
That's right.
I can sense death all the way out here.
I'm afraid of dying.
Was I afraid of it then?
It didn't feel like I was, though.
I cried because I was sad, not scared.
Grandpa's death and the death I face now,
how are they different?
You're a strong kid, so help people.
More of those curses. They're close.
Found them.
He was short-tempered and stubborn.
No one ever paid him a visit but me.
Don't end up like you, huh?
That's okay, but...
Damn it! Is it trying to swallow her along with the cursed object?!
I'm not gonna make it!
Itadori!
I think you had a proper death, Grandpa.
But...
This right here
is just wrong!
So this is a curse?
Not what I was expecting.
Normally I'd be pissed, but good job.
Why're you acting so smug?
By the way, what's that munching on the curse?
My cursed beasts.
You can see them, then?
Normally a curse can't be seen.
Not unless you're on the verge of death or in special places like this.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I've never seen a ghost or anything before tonight.
You're not scared, are you?
Well, I was scared for a bit.
But you know, people actually die.
Huh?
So at the very least,
I want the people I know to have proper deaths.
Not that I really get it myself.
Whoa.
This it?
Yeah.
Special-grade cursed object, Ryomen Sukuna's finger.
It's a miracle it didn't get swallowed.
Why would anything eat it? Does it taste good?
Don't be stupid.
You'd do it to gain stronger cursed energy.
It's dangerous, so hand it over already.
Yeah, yeah.
Run!
Fushiguro!
Nue!
Damn it, I can't think straight!
Itadori!
Why don't you get it?! Just take those two and run!
You're in a tight spot yourself!
Only curses can exorcise other curses!
You can't beat it!
You're telling me that, now?
In any case, you're gonna die at this rate!
If I went home now, I'd be having nightmares!
Besides,
I've actually got...
Help people.
...quite the curse myself!
Dumbass! Hand it over to me or you'll be eaten too!
Why would anything eat it? Does it taste good?
Don't be stupid.
You'd do it to gain stronger cursed energy.
There is a way to save everyone!
I just need some cursed energy, right, Fushiguro?!
Stop.
Don't do it!
Ryomen Sukuna's finger!
That's a special-grade cursed object!
It's a deadly poison! He'll die for sure!
But there is a chance.
A one in a million chance.
Ah, I knew it!
Light feels best in the flesh!
This is messed up!
A one-in-a-million chance worst-case scenario.
The special-grade cursed object has incarnated!
A cursed spirit's flesh is no fun.
Where are the people? The women?!
What a wonderful era to be in.
Women and children are crawling everywhere like maggots.
Marvelous!
It'll be a massacre!
What do you think you're doing with my body?
Give it back.
How are you able to move?
I mean, it's my body.
He's suppressing me?
Don't move.
You're no longer human.
Under Jujutsu regulations, Itadori Yuji,
I will exorcise you as a curse!