Episode 1: Ryoumen Sukuna
Itadori
Miyashiro Prefectural Sugisawa Third High School
Occult Phenomenon
Research Club
Ku
ri
o
ne
Sea Angel
A type of plankton
living in cold oceans!
A transparent
body!
It's actually
related
to mollusks!
It moves its legs,
which look
like wings,
to float around.
When capturing prey,
its mouth pops open
and shoots out tentacles!
Eek!
Notice
Mysterious Events
File 9
Belongings Found
on Roadside,
Possible Crime
Former Employee, Age 35, Goes Missing at Sugisawa
Former Employee of a
Major Construction Company
Never Made a Comeback
and Went Into Debt
Last
Sighted
at
Sugisawa
Third
Laid Off from Work
Failed to Start New Enterprise
Possible Suicide
Laid Off from Work
Failed to Start New Enterprise
Continuous Collection Calls
Threatening Calls and Faxes
Suspicious Men at His Home
Possible Kidnapping
Vengeful Spirit
Hard Ticks
A large,
parasitic tick
that sucks the blood
of animals and humans!
Be careful, because they can be carriers of
infectious diseases that lead to death if they bite humans!
Diseases such as Severe Fever with Thrombocytopenia Syndrome (SFTS)
Hmm?
They leap onto targets
from grass and bushes.
Burp
Leap
Size
Before Blood
After Blood
After sucking blood, their size
can increase up to 100x!
Not Enough Members
Track and Field Coach
Takagi
Itadori
No Unauthorized Entry
*Japan's National Record
*World Record
Shiver
Tremble
3 Days Ago
Occult Phenomenon
Research Club
*World Record
5.47s+
Sugisawa Hospital
Itadori
Saitou
Nurse Call
Matsumoto
Hanai
Eguchi
Akita
Itadori
Kosaka
Notification of Death
4th-grade Girl Commits Suicide. Bullying Suspected.
Suicide Note Read, "They Told Me to Die."
Head of Nursing Home in Mifune Ward Stabbed to Death.
Former Patient Unindicted Once Again
Occult Phenomenon
Research Club
Episode 2:
For Myself