Gotta get it homie
Gotta move it
If you gonna do it then gonna need to prove it
Everybody just talk, nobody really do it
Don't tell anybody until you really do it
Ain't no need to double check with anyone
Use your own judgment and break the walls
Let's do flashy fake
Keep it low
Keep it cool
Gotta prove them wrong
I won't give up the fight in my life
'Cause my life is living for love
Standing off and groove on time
Tokyo prison
I'm going to relight your feelings
When times are gettin' rough
Night and day are fading
I'm going to relight your feelings
There's no time to explain
Lost in your love
Lost in paradise
Night and day are fadin' out
When times gettin' rough
Access to your love
Lost in paradise
Night and day are fadin' out
Keep on dancin' now
Hey
hey
Hey hey