Overflowing beyond the distorted end
The surface tension of life is being spread apart
The surface tension of life is being torn apart
Before I knew it, I was already screaming in pain
It is the only vent for the blood that's boiling inside me
The rope I'm standing on is about to snap
Should I move or should I stay still?
Should I wait or should I take a chance?
None of my options seem to work
Take one more step
Do what needs to be done
No, I’m never going back and I will never regret it
Watch as I change reality even in the face of bitter truths
The world's stained with disasters, grudges and a thousand sins
I'll take them all on just to chase after your voice
Just like that heartless tone ringing like a ruthless gong