Tokyo Metropolitan
Jujutsu Technical High School
Cold
Episode 8:  Boredom
Kabuki-cho First Street
5 min
8th single "Youth Mineral" Release Celebration
Takada-chan
Tall Idol Takada-chan
Takada-chan Personal Handshake Event
One Month Later
Log
——
September 2018
Kanagawa Prefecture, Kawasaki City
Kinema Cinema
Ticket Sales
Now Showing
Playing
After the showing,
three high school boys'
disfigured corpses were discovered by staff
Cause of death: increased cranial pressure and
respiratory paralysis due to cranial deformity
Juju Stroll
Personal Handshake Event
Event Hall
5 min
8th single "Youth Mineral" Release Celebration
Takada-chan
Episode 9:
Small Fry and Reverse Retribution