Itadori, why is his nose bleeding?
Uh, because I punched him.
When?
At the start of our fight.
Did his hand touch you?
Yeah.
My attacks have no effect on him.
Oh?
Wai-What? Why?!
I'll explain while I'm lecturing you.
First, his technique doesn't seem to work on Itadori.
Second, he has a reason not to kill him.
Either way, it works to our advantage.
What I can do is halt his movements.
Once we have created an opening,
we will shower him with a barrage of attacks.
We must exorcise him right here.
Got it!
I need to take out the Seven-Three Sorcerer,
all while keeping an eye on Itadori Yuji.
I had a feeling this would work,
but they just dodged it!
And now they're breaking all the weaker spikes.
I guess it's only good for small fries.
Time to stop!
Right before he changes shape...
...he stores up cursed energy.
Good.
Even in this small form, there's still the risk
of being taken out by Itadori Yuji.
He really is my natural enemy!
Let's keep him busy for a bit.
Transfigured humans! He still had more of them?
Kill that short-haired brat.
I knew it. He doesn't have what it takes to kill a human!
Let's play!
Please...
Kill me...
I'll have him fight you next. I wonder if he'll cry.
He's a stupid brat who can't separate
his ideals from reality.
You're wrong.
He is right in the middle of making that distinction.
If you ask me, I would say you are the stupid one.
Did he kill them?!
His cursed energy level increased?
I'll change shape right before impact—
No time to create substitutes.
What's this feeling?
Such a fresh wave of inspiration!
Is this...
death?
I bet I could do it now.
Domain Expansion:
Self-Embodiment of Perfection!
Shit.
Right now, I have nothing but gratitude for you.
Quit screwing around!
Why did he only trap Nanamin inside?!
This is not good. I have to do something!
Domain Expansion.
Within this Innate Domain
constructed from cursed energy,
all hits are fatal and can not be evaded.
It's the pinnacle of sorcery that I could never attain.
His soul manipulation technique
seems to have a condition for activation:
He must touch the target with his hand.
But in a Domain where I can't avoid his attacks...
I am literally in the palm of his hands.
Idiots.
Jujutsu sorcerers are idiots.
Always ready to sacrifice themselves for others,
forcing their comrades to do the same.
That's why I quit.
Or rather, ran away.
Do you like this casse-croute?
You always buy this one!
Oh, uh, yes.
They stopped selling it
at my local convenience store.
I bet our bread is better, anyway.
Well, you are a bakery.
Whoa, harsh.
Please visit us again!
A Fly Head.
Leaving it alone won't hurt anything.
I'd hate to do something and
be mistaken for some weird exorcist.
Hello, everybody!
Gettin' some sales?!
When people trust us with their money, they're trusting us with their lives.
It goes without saying that
risk and profit is a balancing act.
You don't need to
push yourself too hard at the start.
Just be sincere with the clients.
Never forget that.
Right!
Nanami!
Don't be such a stiff all the time.
You're scaring the virgin.
Listen up, rookie!
What you need to think about,
first and foremost, are the company's profits.
Profit for the company is profit for the customer!
Even when we con the client into
buying dead-end stocks?
Of course!
We're the ones watching the market 'round the clock. We've earned it!
Nanami, it's your second year here!
You're smarter than this. Loosen up a little!
I expect great things from you!
I've never been the type who worries about
the meaning of life or having a purpose for living.
I just want to earn enough money
to retire by the time I'm forty,
and enjoy the rest of my aimless life somewhere with a low cost of living.
It's been four years since I left Jujutsu Tech.
Awake or asleep, all I think about is money.
I don't have to deal with curses or other people as long as I have money.
Money.
Money, money.
As long as I have money...
Are you all right?
Are you getting enough sleep?
What about you?
Looks like your fatigue's been building up.
Oh, you can tell?
My shoulders feel heavy these days,
and I'm barely getting any sleep.
My job involves taking care of rich people's money,
and helping them get even richer.
Or something along those lines.
To be honest, nobody would care if I weren't here.
People who eat bread would be sad
if the bakery was gone, though.
Yet for some reason, my job, which exists outside the cycle of human life, pays better.
When you think about it logically, it makes no sense.
A-Are you flexing on me?
No, I'm not.
I'm sorry, that totally went over my head!
Could you take a step forward, please?
How's your shoulder now?
Well...
Hey, it feels lighter!
If anything feels off, please go to the hospital.
I'll be on my way, then.
Hey, wait!
Hold on!
Um...
Thank you!
Please come visit us again!
"Thank you."
Oh, he didn't hear me?
Thank you!
Please! Visit! Again!
I always thought I was someone who never cared about having a purpose in life.
Hello, it's Nanami. I would like to talk to you.
Sure, I'll stop by Jujutsu Tech tomorrow.
What are you laughing about?
Idle Transfiguration.
It's all thanks to you.
I don't need your gratitude.
I've received plenty of it already.
I have no regrets.
How did he get in?
That's right.
The stronger a barrier is from the inside,
the weaker it is on the outside.
Domains are designed to trap the target inside,
which makes them fairly easy to break into.
Because only harm can come
to those who enter.
With Domains like Infinite Void
and Self-Embodiment of Perfection,
victory is all but guaranteed once the target is trapped.
Itadori, however, is an exception.
Within him dwells a soul that
must not be touched.
What did I tell you?
There wouldn't be a second chance.
There is no one in this world more proud and conceited.
He lives guided only by his pleasure and displeasure.
Which one of you lives and which one of you dies
makes absolutely no difference to me.
Aside from him, I truly don't care about anything else.
What just happened?
I'll kill him!
Domain Expansion really burns through cursed energy.
Definitely a high-risk, high-reward technique.
And that damn Sukuna just...
But this is the moment of truth!
I'll go all out! Use every last bit of my cursed energy!
The target is huge.
His cursed energy is wavering, too.
There's no way he can counter me.
I can land a hit for sure.
It's my last chance.
No more tricks.
Divergent Fist!
What's with the lack of resistance?
Bye-bye!
Hold up!
It was fun.
Ino, the target has escaped into the sewers.
Yes.
Please scour everything from my current location to the southeast.
You could even exorcise him
by yourself right now.
We're going after him too!
Itadori!
Come on! Move, dammit!
Weren't you going to kill that thing?!
Beat him... to a bloody pulp...
Itadori!
So that was the King of Curses, Ryomen Sukuna.
In his current state, his cursed energy
should be lower than Jogo's, and yet...
That presence...
His soul is in a class of its own.
I'm certain now.
Even if we're all wiped out, as long as
Sukuna is resurrected, the age of curses will come.
Still, damn, this sucks.
Right now, I want nothing more than to kill Itadori Yuji!
It's so frustrating!
But whatever.
Unlike his body, I can kill his soul over and over.
How should I kill it next time?
You were told to rest, weren't you?
Is this the lecture?
I'm not in a position to lecture someone
who just saved my life.
I saved you?
Patchwork's technique interferes with the soul.
Since you invaded his Domain,
he wound up touching Sukuna's soul.
I was saved thanks to that.
But I never swapped with him.
Sukuna never came out. Patchwork went to him.
Then it wasn't me who saved you.
He just did it on a whim.
Nanamin, I killed people today.
People die and there's no avoiding it,
but they should at least have a proper death.
That's what I used to think.
That's why I wanted to
keep that trigger from being pulled.
But now that I've pulled it myself,
I don't know anymore.
What is a proper death?
I don't have the answers you're looking for.
Even if we assume that good people dying peacefully and wicked ones being punished is the right way,
most people are neither good nor evil.
Death comes equally for us all,
but it's never the same for any of us.
Trying to guide everyone to
proper deaths sure sounds exhausting.
I personally wouldn't recommend it.
But you'll do it anyway, won't you?
Just don't end up dying in the process.
Just as I needed you to save me today,
there will be many others
who will need you in the future.
You are a jujutsu sorcerer now, after all.
Put it in this box once you've filled it out.
And you don't need to write your name.
You're the one who gave
Yoshino those scars, aren't you, Ito?
I don't wanna hear any bitching from the guy who wimped out at the time.
He quit school and moved away, didn't he?
Who cares?
And what about me?
I've barely been able to
move my left arm since then.
We're talking about your crimes right now.
Reflect on the punishment you've earned for yourself.
And where's your punishment?
Mine starts now. I'll begin to atone
by facing the things I turned a blind eye to.
Both you and I...
will have to bear the sin of killing Yoshino's heart for the rest of our lives.
I'll be watching you, Ito.
I don't understand what a proper death is.
So at least until I do.
Until the day I kill him.
I'll make sure
I won't lose to anything.
Juju Stroll.
Tuna.
Is it ready yet?
Salmon, salmon.
These meatballs are great.
Who made them?
Oh, I did.
They're easy to make.
Bonito flakes.
You can cook for yourself?
Can't say I'm surprised, though.
Actually, Itadori taught me how to make these.
I see.
So this is Itadori's... legacy.
No, not really.
These meatballs are great!
Oh, these are super easy to cook.
Even Fushiguro could make them
after I taught him how.
I can't wait to see those two again!