Gotta get it homie
Gotta move it
If you gonna do it then just get onto it
Everybody just talk
Nobody really do it
Na-Nah you gotta keep it to yourself until you do it
Ain't no need to check with anyone
Use your own judgment and break the walls
Unlike those flashy fakes
Keep it low
Keep it cool
Gotta prove them wrong
I won't give up the fight in my life
'Cause my life is living for love
Standing off and groove on time
Tokyo prison
I'm going to relight your feelings
When times are getting rough
Night and day are fading
I'm going to relight your feelings
There's no time to explain
Lost in your love
Lost in paradise
Night and day are fadin' out
When times are gettin' rough
Access to your love
Lost in paradise
Night and day are fadin' out
Keep on dancin' now
Hey
hey
Hey hey