All mankind is full of bullshit, lies, and empty minds like we're not even alive
I'll live my life caring and open minded till I'm reduced to this hollow
I just don't have the talent to live up to life's unfair expectations
Without a personality, my memories are all I have for a place to be
I'm crying every waking moment
I know what mask I'm supposed to show but still, I wanna hear it from you
Can we end the darkness? Can we cleanse the darkness?
We'll find out when the veil of night falls
Face to face on the path we trace over and over
Let's throw it all away and restart
Don't give up now, don't hold back now
I thought I was stronger than this but I can't stay the same forever
Now I can't imagine there's a future for a cursed man like me
I tried to run but kept falling
Guarding these wounds that will never heal
The world, it waits for me to start giving up