T-minus one minute until we begin.
And now, a word of well-appreciated encouragement from Miss Iori Utahime.
Wha?!
U-Uh...
Um, some degree of injury will be unavoidable,
but, um... let's help each other out...
whenever we can... or something...
All right, time's up.
H-Hey! Gojo, you little—
Now, let the sister school exchange event...
begin!
Respect your seniors!
Ichiro reference?!
How stupid.
Where's Todo?
What makes you think I'd know?
Can't we all just get along?
Where do you think the boss curse is?
It was probably released somewhere in the center.
I doubt it'll sit still, though.
At the designated time,
we'll split into the Panda and
Megumi squads for scouting.
The rest is up to you, Yuji.
Got it!
Where are you going?
That's a small fry.
Panda, stop!
Great! The gang's all here!
Come at me all at once!
Scatter!
He came alone after all.
We were right to switch with Yuji after all.
I already knew it, but he really is a monster.
Yup.
So just ignore him.
Tuna.
Todo will come straight at us.
No doubts about that.
Mai might follow suit and target me, too.
Todo is a monster.
Worst case scenario,
we all face him and we all get wiped out.
So our plan was to leave one person behind, either Panda or Megumi, to keep him occupied.
But we'll leave it to you, Itadori.
We'd rather not lose anyone on the scouting teams.
You don't have to beat him.
Just buy us as much time as you can.
You'll still have to break a leg, though!
To be blunt, we weren't counting on your abilities anyway, so it's okay if you go down.
Rude!
I'm sorry, Megumi.
I bet you wanted your rematch with Todo.
No, I'm good either way.
Man, you're so dry.
But still, if I'm doing this,
I'm gonna win.
Nice speed.
No way! I thought I landed a good one.
Let me return the favor, my junior.
Defend like your life depends on it!
Tell me, where?
My arm's still here, right?
I thought it got blown off.
If that curse didn't get in the way, this could've turned out bad!
Done already?
Now then, who's next?
Are you for real?
You think you can just pound my head like that?!
What if you made me
even dumber than I already am?!
Don't worry about it.
Takada says,
"Men are perfect when they're a little dumb."
Who's that?
I'm not into idol bullshit.
Then how do you know she's an idol?
You know who she is, all right.
What's your name, junior?
Itadori Yuji.
I see. Itadori Yuji.
I have one question for you.
What type of girls do you like?
Huh?
My type?
Why are you asking me that right now?
Don't worry about that.
I'm just appraising you.
I don't really get it, but if I had to say...
A tall girl with a big ass, I guess?
Like Jennifer Lawrence?
This new series is pretty good.
Oh?
I'm gonna confess to Takada.
What?! Don't do that!
I don't wanna have to pick up the pieces!
That's such a pain!
Why are you assuming she'll reject me?
I could ask you why you think she'll say yes.
Anne Sullivan once said to Helen Keller,
"What idiot admits defeat before even trying?"
Inoki was the one who said that.
I'm sorry.
I'm already in love with someone.
Any chance that someone is me?
No way, man.
Come on, let's go.
Ramen is on me.
"Back home, we were invincible…"
Seems like we're best friends!
We literally just met!
Yeah, keep going straight.
Todo is there, though.
Not a problem.
He's the one who told us to do as we pleased.
New Shadow Style: Simple Domain.
Quick Draw!
He's got quick reflexes!
I know I hesitated for a bit,
but my counter didn't even scratch him!
I'm surrounded?
Wait.
Are these guys...
trying to kill me?
What just...
Itadori and I switched places?!
Hey.
I told you I'd kill anyone who got in my way.
No, you didn't.
You said you'd kill us if we ordered you around.
Was that Itadori's...
No, was it Todo's technique?
Yeah, whatever. Piss off!
Looks like we're retreating.
Lame.
Thank goodness!
Make sure you kill him.
That depends on Itadori.
Don't order me around.
What's with these guys?
First they try to kill me and now they're arguing with each other?
After all, I'm not the kind of man
who'd hold back against his best friend!
This is why we should've left him alone.
We're off to a lousy start.
We can't start hunting curses
without me scouting from up here either.
They're all such a hassle.
Hang in there, me.
You're as cute as ever today.
Take her down.
Oh, no.
Mai, Mechamaru. Cover Nishimiya.
Copy that.
I guess we are in trouble without her.
Kamo, are you guys
planning to kill Itadori?
Something's off.
Something's weird.
All the Kyoto students are moving together.
Toward the area we left Yuji in.
I think that puts everyone from Kyoto there?
You mean that's where the target is?
I doubt it.
Unless the second-grade is especially cunning,
my Divine Dog would've noticed it.
They're trying to kill Itadori, don't you think?
What the hell?! That makes no sense!
That is a possibility.
Kelp.
I didn't sense that much hostility from them,
but that was before Yuji's survival surprise.
It's possible if it was on Principal Gakuganji's orders.
Are the Kyoto students the type of cowards
who'd kill someone on command?
They don't see it the same way.
You guys have spent time together with Yuji.
We know he's a good guy too
since we got the chance to meet him.
He's the naturally optimistic type you don't often see among sorcerers.
But the thing is,
to those who don't know anything about Yuji,
the vessel of Sukuna is just an object of fear.
Killing him is no different
from exorcising a curse to them.
Any normal sorcerer could easily blur that line.
We're turning back, Megumi.
Sorry.
What are you apologizing for, dummy?
No point in winning or losing
if your friend ends up dead.
Nobara and I will go back to confirm that Yuji is safe.
He's not answering his phone.
Toge, you keep hunting curses, please.
Bonito flakes!
I know you're worried about Yuji too.
But if my prediction is correct,
the Kyoto students are trying to use the chaos of team battle to assassinate Yuji.
I think they'll call it off once the team battle's over.
Makes sense.
Salmon.
I'm worried about Maki as well.
We won't let them kill Yuji
and we'll win this team battle, too!
Damn straight.
Don't make me call again, Fushiguro!
Also, why didn't they provide us with
wireless radios or Bluetooth earbuds anyway?!
No, thank you! They're distracting,
and they startle me when I get a call.
Then turn it off during combat!
Ow...
So that's Fushiguro's Nue?
Electrified wings.
Looks like I won't be able to move for a while.
Nishimiya, dear!
Come out and play!
So crass!
How not cute.
Kamo, are you guys planning to kill Itadori?
What if I said we were?
You failed, then.
There's no way he'd get taken out so quickly.
We have no reason to kill him.
Yes, you do.
The higher-ups and the Three Great Clans have plenty.
What splendid toughness!
He's actively using the
environment to his advantage!
He's gone?
He's quick enough to think a step ahead!
And to top it off...
he has such tremendous power!
His raw strength is greater than mine,
despite his small body!
Which is why his blows are effective with so little cursed energy!
The lack of cursed energy
makes it harder to read his movements!
But the way his cursed energy hits after a time lag...
that's just... it's just...
wrong!
Was that Todo?
Seems like it.
I think I understand why you failed to finish off Yuji.
So why did you distance yourself from Noritoshi?
Hiding your technique from your allies?
I'm sorry about what's happening with Itadori.
It might sound like an excuse, but I'm not like them.
That said, I don't plan on handing over victory to you.
You know how sorcerers get promoted through a recommendation system, right?
A lot of sorcerers follow
and discuss the exchange event.
If you perform well here,
you're given more chances
to advance while studying.
By the way, you can't be recommended by your own teacher.
For example, Mr. Gojo can't
recommend Itadori to be a first-grade.
I want to be independent and start making money as soon as possible.
Why?
I'm poor!
And I have two little brothers!
Are you okay?
Do you even get along with Mai?
Aren't you too nice a person?
Huh? Probably...
I won't hold back, y'know.
Not a problem!
That's not why I said all that, anyway!
My friend!
That cursed energy you blast with a time lag, that's a bad habit of yours!
You mean my Divergent Fist?
What's he on about all of a sudden?
So long as you're satisfied with that,
you'll never beat me!
If you're content with staying on that level,
our friendship won't last for long.
Are you okay with that?!
I dunno. I don't care, really.
Are you okay with being weak?!
Hell no!
That's the spirit!
My best friend!
Juju Stroll.
Someone who's stronger than me,
at the very least.
Huh? What makes you think I'll answer?
I absolutely can not stand a UBSSD.
Do you know who Sebastian Stan is?
He's totally hot!
Well, you know,
I like hot guys, like most girls.
But I want someone
who is fun to be around too.
And he must make me feel like
he's the only one for me!
Oh, gosh, how embarrassing!
Uh, you know, uh, um...
Wh-Who was it?
Um...
Um, um, um...
You know, that girl who seemed nice.
The nice one.
The one with the bangs.
C'mon, you know which one!
Nice girl...
Oh, Miwa?
Yeah! Her, her, her, her, her!