Exception
Episode 14: Kyoto Sister School Exchange Event - Group Battle 0 -
"I thought you were dead..."
Touching Reunion
With Friends
"Nice to meet you!!"
Deciding Factor of His First Impression,
First Meeting With the Second Years
Kyoto Students Appear!!
Exchange Event Begins!
"Beginner's Guide to
the Exchange Event"
Kyoto
Come have fun in Kyoto
The Complete Guide
Fortunes
Ueno Specialty
Panda
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Second-Year
Zenin Mai
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Third-Year
Toudou Aoi
Nishimiya Momo
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Second-Year
Ultimate Mechamaru
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Third-Year
Kamo Noritoshi
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto Second-Year
Miwa Kasumi
Jujutsu Tech, Semi-First-Grade Sorcerer
Kyoto School Leader
Iori Utahime
Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto School Principal
Gakuganji Yoshinobu
Itadori Rejoins
Jujutsu Technical High School
Tokyo-Kyoto Sister School Exchange Event
Wacky
Cursed Spirit Exorcism Race
Second-Grade
Tokyo Side Meeting
Kyoto Side Meeting
Juju Stroll
Sushi Eishuu
Episode 15:
Kyoto Sister School Exchange Event - Group Battle 1 -